It's time to continue the Kerbal Space program.
Cheers, everybody.
I was supposed to stream like an hour ago, but I got delayed.
I'm sorry.
Well, not that you knew, except that I was, you know, hinting at it in the Discord.
So I probably should just stop doing that.
This is probably why game developers don't announce the release date of their game until they're absolutely sure, you know?
If you announce something, ah.
It's never good.
I'm doing great.
Thank you, Beth.
How about yourself?
For some reason, there's something off about the... Am I sounding normal?
Were you running to the store to get a drink?
I actually was, but I was not running, and it was a while ago.
But yes, I went to the store to get this drink.
I did not add any mods.
I did check out Chattera, by the way, and it's awesome.
The thing is, if I was playing this game off-stream by myself, I would definitely use it.
You know?
But since I'm streaming it, and I'm constantly talking, I think it's gonna get old pretty quick, you know, to have those voices coincide with my voice.
So because of that, I chose not to include it.
But if I was playing this on my own, you bet I would play with it, because it's awesome.
Great mod.
Yeah, exactly.
I am the Chattera.
So solid recommendation from you guys.
Very solid.
I also activated Advanced Tweakables.
I'm not sure what that did.
It didn't allow more things to be tweaked.
I don't know.
But I activated Show Extended Burn Indicator.
I also found the keybind for resetting the camera.
So, for example, if I focus on something, and I just want to get back to my vessel...
I haven't tried it yet, but I assume it's gonna work.
Someone on the comment said it, so I trust it.
And yes, I am aware at this point that I can change the altitude by clicking on a certain HUD icon.
Okay, I get it.
You guys need to calm the hell down, man.
I was doing great without... even without that.
Like, you're all acting like I can't play the game without knowing that.
Didn't I do final till now?
Come on.
Jesus Christ.
Anyway.
How are you all doing?
Everything okay?
What's the latest and greatest?
How about Science Notification?
I don't know what you mean by that.
I didn't install whatever that is.
I did, of course, modify the custom mods a little bit.
By the way, I am working on getting those out to you guys as well, because you've expressed an interest.
The thing is, though, I don't want to just put something out there that's trash, you know?
If I put something out there for other people to use, I want to quality test that for a while.
You know, really make sure that it works, because right now it is working on my computer, yes, with my hardware, with my insane GPU, of course.
So I'm trying to make it run better, more performance.
I'm trying to make it work without restock as well, because it would break without that, you know?
Just trying to make it better and actually quality test it, if I put something out there.
So it's coming.
I just don't want to, you know, put shit out there, pretty much.
I don't want to put out AI slop, right?
I want to put out AI quality, if anything.
You know what I mean.
I'm going to skip school to watch this, I don't care.
No, San Pao Duro, underscore.
You better get out of here right now and go to school.
What do you mean?
I can't be responsible for you missing school.
That's crazy.
What's the name of the SRB smoke mod?
Well, I call it Solid Rocket Plumes.
Custom mod.
It's coming out.
It's actually been optimized so crazily that it's barely taken up a couple milliseconds every frame, no matter how much smoke there is.
It's crazy how performant it is right now.
From any angle, looking straight down the column, from inside the plume, outside, fucking wherever.
It's insane.
But I'll make it even better.
What are we playing today?
We're playing Kerbal Space Program, my good friend.
Haugol, is how I'm going to pronounce your name.
That's a nice name.
Can you play a Minecraft horror mod?
I could, but then I would get the cops called on me.
Last time I played a horror game, Five Nights at Freddy's, my neighbors, you know, came at my door with pitchforks.
It was not a good time.
It's not going to work where I live right now, unfortunately.
Let's conquer Minmus.
I think I already kind of did, but we're going to do it, of course, even more.
We're going to go back to Minmus.
I'm also going to do stuff with my space station.
And last time I discovered something called KerbNet, and I'm insanely hyped about that.
Wow, I actually read you typing hype right when I said hype.
That's kind of hype.
When are you adding Jackie into KSP?
Well, they're already making a Jackie KSP, aren't they?
Kitten Space Agency is actually a thing.
It's coming at some point, I guess.
So, maybe at that time, I'll put Jackie in there.
That's perfect, isn't it?
I love that they're working on something more like this.
Because this game, yeah, it may be a little niche, right?
But, holy shit, it's good.
That's like my new obsession.
Will you play KSA?
If it's good, yeah, of course.
If you love KerbNet, you should look into ScanNet.
It's so...
Is that like...
Are you saying that there's something else in the game called that?
Because don't tell me anything about the game.
I would love to figure that out on my own, you know?
Unless you're mentioning like a mod or something.
Let me at least experience KerbNet before you suggest mods already changing that.
You know what I mean?
Otherwise, I won't even know what the differences are.
Yeah, okay.
I figured it was a mod.
Just checking.
There was something else that I checked out as well.
Another mod.
I forgot what it was.
Oh, god.
I don't remember now.
But dude, dude, modding this game is actually insane.
Like, the amount of stuff that people have made for this game is absolutely incredible.
Modding is the best thing ever.
It really is.
For this game especially, it's...
It's wild.
Oh, man.
Let me put on some...
Kerbal Space Program music.
I actually added some more tracks to this.
Because, you know, may as well add more space-related tracks.
More variety, the better.
You might be using GitHub.
Yeah, but right now they're all private.
Well, mostly I just commit locally, you know?
And then when I really know something I'm gonna use later or something, then I put on GitHub.
You're like top ten people on Earth right now.
No, I'm not.
Hey, what did I tell you?
Go to school.
What are you doing here?
Sam Pauduro underscore.
You need to go to school.
Close this stream.
I don't want to see you chatting again.
Come on.
You can watch the VOD later.
Join the VOD gang.
I'm just kidding.
I'm not your mom.
You can do whatever you want.
I'm just trying to be the, you know, the good conscience on your shoulder.
Telling you what to do.
Ban him so he has to go to school.
I don't think banning someone actually prevents them from watching the stream.
I think they can still watch the stream, no?
I mean, otherwise you just open the page in another browser without being logged in.
I mean, you can't prevent someone from watching a stream.
Just removes chat abilities?
Yeah, okay.
I figured.
Plume mod is coming.
So I'm going to put out the Plume mod, the Parachute mod, which I've also made so much better now, by the way.
Like, all the bugs are ironed out and it's looking so much better.
It's crazy.
You guys are going to be excited, I think.
I think it's really cool.
I'm having a lot of fun with that.
Just messing around with it, you know?
Okay.
Here we go.
I need to actually figure out exactly what I want to do today.
So, last time, we ended up by docking with the little space station thing we have up there.
In fact...
Let me go take a look at that.
That's got to be it right there, huh?
Space station docker.
So, we currently have...
Uh, who is it?
Is it Carson?
Who's in there?
Someone's in here.
Yeah, it's Carson Kerman.
Oh, by the way, I put a timer.
Uh, let me see here.
In one hour and 16 minutes-ish, I'm gonna have to take a break, because I need to hang up my clothes that are in the washing machine right now.
Otherwise, they get musty and nasty.
I already forgot them once in the last 24 hours, so I'm re-washing them now.
I don't want to make the same mistake again.
Okay, um...
So, Carson is in this right now.
And...
Well, we have a problem.
We don't have a lot of fuel.
So, if we want to get this guy back, we either have to come up here and bring him back, or just let him be here for a while.
I mean...
It's like a mini space station at this point, you know?
There's two pots.
I would say that's a space station.
He has, you know, cable connections where he can watch TV.
He's got little snack bowls here.
And some other things.
He's gonna have fun up here.
Isn't that right, Carson?
He's excited.
I mean, look at him.
Okay, I'm just gonna leave you to it.
I'll leave you to it.
Let's see what the...
We have 200 science!
What the fuck?
How come I...
Didn't I...
Spent that last time or something?
Or maybe I was saving it.
I think I was saving it, actually.
Yeah, I'm gonna save it for one of these.
What was it?
Ah, but to do that, we gotta upgrade this facility, and that costs...
Let me check.
A lot of money!
Maybe we can borrow some money.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's just do contract, shall we?
In fact, we have four contracts.
Bring green sandstone back with you.
Moon's stone.
This one is...
I don't know.
We gotta find these...
places here.
Oh, by the way!
And I think I know how to do it now.
We gotta bring a curb net thingy up there so we can scan the surface and figure out where the polar lowlands are, the Farsight Crater or East Crater biomes.
And then we, you know, bookmark it or whatever it's called, and then we fly there.
We also gotta plant the flag on Minmus.
Mystery goo observations from the surface of Minmus.
Okay, easy.
Maybe there's more Minmus stuff.
position satellite in a specific orbit of Minmus.
Build a new orbital station around Minmus!
Dude, I kinda wanna do this.
Build a new station that has an antenna, has a docking port, and can generate power.
That's exactly the type of space station I have around Kerbin right now.
The station must be fully assembled when launched.
Hmm?
I guess you can't stage away...
No, wait, what?
I'm actually confused about that.
So the station that has...
the antenna, docking port, and, I guess, solar panel...
cannot be disassembled before reaching Minmus?
No, all it needs to be is to be assembled when launched.
Okay, so I guess we can disassemble it later?
Oh, I see what they're saying.
They're saying I can't just combine things in orbit up there and say, now I did it.
It has to be, like, a fully, you know, self-sustaining station.
I see.
Have a facility supporting at least eight Kerbals?
Wait, eight Kerbals?
Eight?
Okay, we get 220,000...
Guys, we're doing this.
Are you kidding me?
Have 4,000 units of liquid fuel in your...
Dude, this is kind of crazy.
Maintain stability for 10 seconds.
Put your station in orbit of...
Oh my god.
Yes!
Absolutely.
Uh, what's this?
Docking on or around the moon?
Okay, okay, we don't do that right now.
It's not even that much money.
Uh, yeah.
So, eight Kerbals.
You what, mate?
Do we even have anything or facilities that can support that?
Payload?
Maybe.
Can you consider a Kerbals a payload?
There's also a bunch of stuff I just haven't tried yet because it costs money.
Thermal...
Like, okay, why would I ever use this?
There's gotta be, like, an overheating mechanic of, like, electronics then.
Otherwise, this wouldn't be in the game, right?
Oh, wait!
No, no, no.
It's because I don't have a pod here.
That's why it's, like, grayed out, you see?
Okay, so I did try a lot of these.
Science Junior.
Cargo.
Oh my god.
I mean, we're going to Minmus anyway, right?
Crew cabin.
Crew capacity 2.
That's not even that much.
Wait, I need to see if there's something I can get in Science right now that will allow me to get a lot of Kerbals.
Like, we gotta pack them in tight.
You know how they stack Coca-Cola cans for shipping?
That's what I'm thinking, but Kerbals instead.
Of course, we'll make it comfortable.
This one.
But maybe there's better.
Oh, wait, these I can't get anyway.
So it has to be in here.
This is just one.
Ah, that's fuel.
Okay, I think it has to be this.
Yeah.
I gotta do it.
We're gonna get Science when we get to Minmus anyway.
So we're gonna, you know, have enough for when we finally afford this.
Hopefully.
Okay, well, eight Kerbals, dude.
Eight?
So I guess we can have a pod that has two already.
Yeah, this one.
This one has two.
We can also have one in here.
Wait.
So this one.
And wait a second.
Are we going to come back with this at all?
If it's a space station around Minmus, it's gonna stay there, so no parachutes.
And by the way, I thought about this.
Remember last time when I launched up Carson?
And I was panicking because...
Oh shit, what if we don't get to orbit?
He's dead, you know?
We could have just jumped out with him and used his parachute because they carry personal parachutes.
So we always have that option.
So maybe I don't do this.
I get the...
Yeah, I get this one.
Crew cabin.
I'm looking for the docking thingy.
Coupling.
Yeah.
There we go.
So that's good.
No parachutes on this one.
Yeah, I guess we don't even need a heat shield then either.
This is kind of funky.
Also, I need to double check this.
At least eight kerbals.
5,000 units of electric charge?
Also, 4,000 units of liquid fuel.
Let me actually see these.
Ah, okay.
So it's this number here.
45.
Holy shit.
Wait, can I even do that?
How much is this?
That's 1440?
Guys, we may have a problem here.
How the hell are we gonna get that to Minmus?
Wow.
Uh, well, we're gonna, we're gonna try, I guess.
I feel like I fucked up taking that contract.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
How much is this?
540?
It's nothing.
Uh, also, uh, let me see this thing down here.
Utility.
Oh, it's massive!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
That's actually kind of sweet.
So we can do this.
And
how about, wait a sec.
Question.
If I do this, I'm not sure this fuel can connect with that.
If I put, like, a, uh, engine there, that may not work.
Maybe we need this.
Huh?
Why won't you do that?
Say what now?
I don't understand.
Maybe, maybe that's not how you do it.
So wait, this is, how much?
Oh my god.
Dude, we need like, oh, I think we're cooked?
This, this is, uh,
we can't do this contract.
Also, we need eight kerbals.
Like, hello?
We need like, two of these.
Maybe I'll rotate them to make them look.
No, no, no, actually.
I see ladders.
Okay, well, right now we can support eight.
So the kerbals are taken care of.
Right now we have like, almost 2,000 liquid fuel.
Um, right.
Wait, this is insane.
That's an insane contract.
Oh, let me just naively add more.
So, can I like, see how much we have total?
Oh, cannot trap unused liquid fuel resources?
Oh, right, I don't have an engine.
Okay, okay, got it.
Oh my god, uh, so wait, we guys, I guess we gotta do math in our heads.
So let's approximate this as, uh, 2,800, these two, plus this, it's like, uh, 3,000.
Wait, that's insane.
I need, we really need this?
You gotta be kidding me.
Also, what's this?
Why doesn't it say how much fuel it has?
Oh, it does.
540.
Hey, that's actually, that's actually pretty cool.
Did we need to have that amount of fuel on board?
In your station.
Wow.
Okay, you know what, maybe we drop this, because I, I don't trust this, disconnect here between, the fuel tanks.
It don't make sense to me.
Maybe I can use something like this instead.
Although I don't, oh, that looks cool.
Mark 1 stack tricoupler?
Let me try this one.
Oh my god, it's tiny.
Gotta be that one then.
No!
Brother, are you serious?
What about this one?
No!
Wasting all my money.
Strut connector.
Shit!
Never mind, I go back to the thing.
Wait, I know how we can check this.
See this?
I'm gonna put an engine.
This is a big one.
So it says 4,400 right now.
Aha!
Ah!
It does say more delta V, so I think it actually does somehow connect.
Okay.
That's good.
So right now we have one, two, three, we have definitely have over 4,000 now.
And, we can use some of this on the way up, I think, and we should still be okay.
Okay.
Um, dude, I'm actually gonna pull up my calculator on my phone.
Hold on.
Uh, calculator.
So we have, how much is in one?
1440.
times 4.
That's 5,700.
Plus, 540.
Wait, 6,300.
Units of liquid fuel here.
So we can, actually just, I'm gonna, I'm gonna keep it like this.
Do we even have, ha!
Thrust to weight ratio is below one.
Yeah, okay, so let's put some boosters on this bad boy.
In fact, this is actually not that bad.
The rocket itself becomes the station, which is, I don't know if that's great or not, but, it's fine.
I guess.
Um, but, there is one issue.
This is not a multi-stage rocket, like this, this, we need some insane boosters on this bad boy.
Uh, let's see here.
Coupling.
Also, it's gonna be an expensive boy.
I'm gonna save four of these.
Right there.
Because we need a lot.
Oh, stop doing that.
Uh, okay.
Wait, why is this, oh, oh, I see, I see, I see.
1.8, okay, okay, okay.
That could work.
This is like, 60,000 for a rocket.
What if you fail this?
It's gonna be so expensive.
Also, no.
It's weighing too much.
Wait a sec.
You kidding me?
Is it, oh, it's the pad.
No!
Guys, I think we're cooked.
We cannot do this mission.
We need this upgrade to even do this.
Like, it's impossible.
Otherwise,
it really is.
Actually, wait a second.
Hold on.
I have an idea.
Wait, what's this?
Oh, that's the one I currently have.
I see, I see.
Ah, goddammit.
Okay, okay.
I guess we're just gonna land on Minmus then.
And do the science contracts and all that.
Yeah, it'll bring home some bacon.
It's good.
We can wait with, I mean, we don't have to do that contract now anyway.
We're gonna call this, uh, Minmus, uh, nasty contract.
Uh, to be determined, I guess.
Save that.
Okay, let's just reset this completely.
And let's see what else we can do here.
So, we gotta go to Minmus, we gotta land, we gotta plant a flag, and surface deployed mystery goo, okay.
In fact, why don't I just load one of the other ones I have?
Which one?
What about the Minmus science vessel?
Oh, this is already great.
I think this is the one I made for Minmus, and then I went to moon instead.
For some reason.
But this was actually a solid rocket.
I like this one.
And in here, we have all these instruments.
It's very nice.
And the good news is, we can bring Bob.
And a pilot.
Wait, we need to make this not snap.
There we go.
Perfectly aligned.
Nice.
Okay.
So that's looking nice.
Um, didn't we also unlock some new things?
Maybe we can bring something new.
Electrical.
Oh, wait, we need some...
I did bring a battery.
We can actually put a little solar panel on it, I guess.
No reason not to, right?
Let's put one...
here.
Nah.
I mean, we have enough battery.
This guy's gonna add weight and shit.
We don't need that.
Uh, okay.
So mystery goo, check, we have that.
I still don't think we can actually get this, uh, stone, because I think we may need the surface sample thingy.
Yeah.
And, uh,
that's pretty good.
Looking sexy.
I really like these boosters on the side.
They look really nice.
Okay, anything else I should be bringing?
All kinds of hinges.
Maybe, like, a reaction wheel?
Wait!
I feel like we should bring a Science Junior.
Imagine how much science that's gonna be on Minmus.
Right?
How are we gonna fit this bad boy?
Payload.
Oh, no.
This is the problem with this.
It's too tiny.
Like, it doesn't fit anywhere here that's nice.
I mean, I can put it there.
But that is an atrocity.
Absolutely not.
How am I gonna...
Maybe I can put it in here?
Is that cheeky?
No, there's no space for that.
Bit too ambitious.
Uh, let me put this battery over here.
There we go.
Oh, no, it's clipping through!
Emergency!
We have crimes.
There we go.
Fixed!
I'm gonna save this.
The MSV is almost ready for launch.
Ba-bam!
And we are within limits.
Wonderful.
Okay, man.
Maybe I add a little bit of, uh, aerodynamicism.
Maybe some winglets.
Oh, wait, what's this?
The locks winglets!
Oh, yeah.
Why not?
I'll add a bunch.
Three, four.
Oh, that looks good!
Oh, my God!
Tell me that isn't sexy.
Holy shit!
Man, what a beaut.
Okay.
Let's just go.
Uh, crew, cargo, and bill.
Uh, no, we need Bob.
Actually, hold on.
So, the crew is fixed.
I need to figure out if there's a way to bring this, um, science junior.
Maybe we can somehow...
I was thinking this, maybe.
Wait.
How would that, um...
Wait, how does that work?
Wait, no.
Oh, right.
Okay, okay, okay, so it goes up.
But I need it to go down.
Can I just do that?
Ooh, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Wait, hold on, is it that simple?
Check this out.
Science guy there.
And,
wait, no, stop, stop.
How do I stop?
Turn, left alt, oh, oh, I see, I see, left alt.
Oh my God, that's amazing.
Oh wait, that looks weird now.
How do I fix that?
Oh no.
Edit fairing.
Dude, I wish I could somehow snap to this bottom part here.
Ah, wait, maybe I can.
If I do this now, then I right click, and then edit fairing.
Build fairing.
And then, what was it?
Alt.
Why doesn't it work?
Oh, I, okay, I see.
Ah, I can't actually do that.
Maybe I go a little wider then?
Like, oh, that's weird.
This doesn't feel intended.
I feel like I'm sort of breaking rules.
Oh, no, no, there we go, there we go.
Nice.
Holy shit, that looks amazing.
Let's see if it flies correctly though.
Okay, so hold on.
So these three, 1.5, that's perfect.
They get detached.
Beautiful.
And then, this and that.
And then the, uh, fairing.
And then this one.
Okay, so that's...
Wait, so we do this one?
Let me check if I have a heat shield here.
Oh, I think, yeah, that's a heat shield.
Okay, good.
So that one gets detached.
And it's parachutes.
Oh, wait, no, this fairing needs to be further down.
I guess we can put those together?
Wait, this is gonna be so weird.
Something's off about this.
This is gonna be an ugly-ass rocket.
You know what?
Maybe we can look...
We can make it look cooler.
I'm gonna...
Can I, like, hide the thingy?
What does clamshell deploy?
Clamshell.
I'm thinking of a clam.
Okay, with the pearl inside?
So it's, like, opening in one direction only, or what?
Truss structure.
Oh, cool, you can even...
Oh.
Wait, what?
Oh, that's cool!
Oh, I like that.
Make it golden.
The golden pearl is in there.
In the clamshell.
That's amazing!
Uh...
Okay, save.
This is...
Dude, I'm so proud of this rocket.
This is my masterpiece so far.
I mean, look at it.
It's beautiful.
It's performant.
It's just everything you could ever want in a rocket.
I'm not too happy about this part still.
This is still a little janky feeling.
I feel like I'm, like, hacking the game a little bit.
Like, it feels hacky.
It doesn't feel intended.
You know what I mean?
Okay.
Now.
Uh...
I think we're ready.
It's just about time to go.
Cheers.
Okay.
Uh...
Let's go.
Cargill and Bob.
Bob.
We're about to set off on a great adventure.
Actually, I'm gonna do this.
So, look at this here.
This is sea level, and now we have land.
That's cool.
Good to know.
So now you guys can, uh, stop commenting about that on YouTube.
I got it now.
Okay, here we go.
Three, two, one.
Lift off of the MSV!
On its way to Minmus.
To conduct science experiments and fulfill contracts.
Basically, we gotta bring home the bacon.
The bosses demand it.
It's a beautiful day for a launch.
I'm gonna start turning.
Now.
But slightly.
We're gonna make the perfect frickin' burn here.
More perfect than anything you've ever seen.
Wait, why does it wanna do that?
I thought it would be more stable with the fins, but I guess not.
It's still wanting to go nuts here.
Okay, we gotta turn even more now.
Okay, soon time to detach.
Kind of wanna try and detach before they run out to see what happens.
Bye-bye!
See ya, friend!
We see you begin!
Okay, it's kinda stabilizing on its own now.
I need to see apoapses.
Okay, 42.
And a little higher.
Dude, this burn has been perfect so far!
Holy shit!
55.
We're gonna end up precisely where we want.
Let's see if we can get to orbit with this stage.
Oh, shit.
62.
Okay, we gotta go a little more up here.
I'm trying to aim for 70-ish.
70.
Stop the engine.
Let's see.
Oh, yeah.
I can actually...
Oh, wait.
I have 1000 delta V left here.
It's actually not enough.
It's gonna be close, but it's not enough.
Which means we're gonna have to use the next stage, which is gonna be slower, so we're gonna have to burn earlier.
I'm gonna say...
now.
Burn horizontal.
Cargill is a pro at this.
Holy shit.
Dude, I...
I love this game!
Oh!
I just got so excited.
Come on.
Actually, maybe we can...
No, no.
I mean, numbers are not gonna lie.
We have 350 delta V left.
It's not enough.
But, you know, a part of me still hopes that it is enough.
Okay.
Time to do this!
We're almost in orbit.
The moon.
It's not our destination.
We're going for Minmus.
Dude, I shit you not, I bought some candy the other day at the store that looks exactly like Minmus.
It was the sour candy I was talking about.
I'll take a picture of it next time I buy it so you can see what I mean.
Like, it's even bumpy in the same way.
Oh, shit.
We need to start.
Okay, here we go.
Not the perfect orbit, but, you know, it'll have to do.
Okay, so Minmus.
You bastard.
Target.
And I need to test this new keybind that I made.
So, if I do this and then I do...
Oh, nice!
Oh, that's gonna be so helpful.
I am so...
Oh, wait, wait.
Hold on.
Inclination.
Right.
Okay, so we're approaching the sending node.
Let's try and burn downwards here then.
Of course, there's no down and up in space, but...
Right now, there is.
No, up.
We need to burn up, actually.
Oh, wait.
Someone also mentioned in the comments you can somehow click on something to have it, like, be pinned.
I forgot.
Guys, Rotund, can you tell me how to do this?
Apparently, you can pin this thing and I need to know how to do it.
You can tell me.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna open chat.
Oh, right click?
Okay, okay.
Let me see.
Well, there it is!
Okay, great!
Thank you.
Also, I kind of want to find that information here.
Approach Info Orbit I'm trying to find where this number, the minus 5.6 degrees, is located down here.
But I'm not...
Oh, I also see more stuff here.
Look at this!
Okay, so I'm gonna go up.
Oh, it's even gonna tell me exactly.
Go to zero.
Oh, there we go.
Okay, so we start with this burn.
So we need to burn 221.
Wow.
Burn time.
Oh!
It even tells me when to start burn!
Ah-ha!
Now I don't have to do the crazy head math of dividing by 2.
That's okay.
So we...
Let me aim towards the thing.
Oh, I need to...
I guess I don't need to right-click anymore.
Wait.
Is it...
Oh!
I like that the arrow is just pointing me to it.
How are we doing on battery?
300 battery.
We are totally chilling and cooking and...
baking and all the other things in the kitchen.
Uh-oh.
Come on!
Get on target!
On program.
3...
2...
1...
Made it!
Now, you...
You better keep that thing right there, buddy.
Come on.
Come on, you.
There we go.
Done.
So now we should have the same inclination.
Great.
And then we can start burning!
So let's see here.
Uh, it's already our target, so we now burn like here.
But we can always adjust it.
This is the cool thing about this.
Prograde until we get an approach.
Oh, that's the moon.
Don't want to accidentally...
Actually, it's fine.
There we go!
And now I need to do...
I guess that works.
Wait, I actually can't see shit still.
Uh, keybind.
Click on this thing again.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Approach 1.
150...
Oh wait, is that for the...
Oh, that's maneuver one.
Okay, okay.
So we're gonna go like this.
Let me just see what happens.
Wait, I don't think this is actually showing me.
Man, this fucking...
UI is confusing me a little bit.
Okay, 1.4...
So it is this one.
I guess we need to burn a little like that.
So...
Oh wait, can I...
See, the problem is it focuses on this over here now when I really need to have my camera over there.
I wish I could just sort of free-move the camera.
It's driving me crazy.
God damn it.
Oh wait.
Oh god.
I am not a fan of the maneuver mode.
I really am not.
I feel like I should just wing it.
It feels so janky, doesn't it?
Like, it's just stacked on top of each other all these UI elements.
Also, why is my shit so fucked here?
Oh, that's my escape.
Okay, so I get pulled by Minmus when I come close and it messes up my orbit on my return trip.
I also don't understand...
Okay, you know what?
This is fine.
This is the burn we're doing.
In five minutes.
Let's aim towards the thing we need to aim.
Get ready.
Okay.
Five minutes.
Speeding up.
Oh, I can just click here.
You ready?
In seven seconds.
Two.
One.
We have started the burn.
Making my way to Minmus.
That's a long burn.
Are you excited, Carson?
You get to eat candy today.
Sour candy.
You can fill your mouth with it.
I'm trying to adjust this a little bit.
Okay, we're almost there.
And we still have a lot of fuel.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Dope.
Looks good to me.
I mean, we're gonna have an encounter.
We're just gonna improvise when we get there.
That's really the way I should be thinking about this.
As long as we can get to the sphere of influence, we're fine.
You know?
Okay, now I want to test something, though.
Whoa!
They got shot!
To hell and back.
Actually, they don't come back.
Well, we can duck material study.
That's not a lot of science.
But what we can do is we can transfer it.
Let me do...
Oh my god.
Malfunctioning!
Get out of here.
Okay, so what do we got?
This thing, transfer data.
I'm gonna transfer that to this thing.
And then we need to do...
that one.
But I think I already got this science.
Yeah, we're not gonna bother with that.
Okay.
Bob, you're up!
It's time for you to go reset.
Let go.
We can also...
do this.
Oh yeah.
We're on our way to Minmus right now.
We're gonna perform some...
resetting here.
Restore.
Back inside.
Wait, where's the hatch?
Oh, okay.
Easy peasy.
And I don't think I need to do any of this.
Yeah, yeah.
We're gonna do it when we get there.
I wonder if the structural stability of this is sound, you know?
I don't know if this can sort of snap if there's enough forces.
I don't know if that's actually modeled or something.
Okay, go.
We're on our way.
Moving through space at thousand X.
In fact, I don't even need to see this target anymore.
Let's go faster.
We're gonna be coming in hot here.
Let's see if we can see the moon.
Look at that!
We got the moon there and we got Kerbin.
And there's Minmus.
Getting closer.
Cheers.
God, it's so tiny.
It totally looks like that candy.
I wanna eat it so bad.
Okay, we're slowing down automatically.
That means we're approaching another Conic.
We're gonna burn a Periapsis.
Hoi-hoi-hoi!
Slow down!
Here we go.
We're gonna turn Retrograde.
It's gonna take a while because we're a big thick boy.
And let's try to land on the lid side here.
Wait, something's wrong.
Ah!
It wouldn't show me the Periapsis until I actually am in a stable orbit.
I was like, why isn't this show...
But that's because I was on an escape trajectory.
I see.
Let's get it down to like...
Actually, I don't mind...
Right there.
Oh, dude.
Let's land here.
Ooh, that looks nice.
Where is it?
Oh, that's the plane.
Oh, God.
Oh, there it is.
Why is the camera like this?
So confusing.
Reset that.
Oh, wait.
We're coming the other way around.
Whoops.
Miscalculated.
How's our battery?
Plenty battery.
We gotta go a little more around first.
That's probably fine.
Speeding up.
Oh, we're approaching.
Hoi!
Also, I need to remember...
Uh...
Collect surface-deployed mystery goo.
Right, we got that.
Moonstone.
We don't need that.
This one, maybe we can do.
I don't know.
And I guess the flag.
Plant the flag.
Yeah.
Okay, so before we do anything right now, I'm actually gonna go to the lid side here.
Hide that.
Okay.
Turn retrograde.
And then while we're doing this, I'm gonna conduct study here.
This is gonna give us a lot.
Ah, okay.
Not that much.
I guess we already did this when we did the flyby of Minmus.
Right.
That's okay.
I'll take it.
We can transfer that to our little container.
What about these measurements?
Nothing.
Which means there's probably nothing on the other ones.
Yeah.
Mystery goo?
Oh, a little bit of science.
I'll take that.
And now we need Bob to go on EVA again because he's the man.
He gets to do all the EVA action.
Bob, I need you to put your finger in this thing right here.
Don't question it.
Just do it.
Oh, and also...
Oh, wait!
I have to collect it first.
There we go.
Now we reset.
Now this thing...
We already did transfer the data, so, yeah, restore.
And the other ones are fine, I think.
God, this view is insane from here.
I mean, look at that.
Just imagine...
See the other planets over there?
Damn.
Okay, begging.
Time to land!
Let's figure this out.
I kind of want to land in these places.
So, retrograde.
Looks good.
Okay.
We're going to really try to land in there.
There's only, like, a tiny sliver here of this.
Whoa, what is that?
Look at that over there.
Some kind of blemish on it.
Would be cool to investigate that, too.
Going to burn retro again.
We're actually just going to burn until the line points at the ground.
It's that simple.
Like there.
It's going to become even more this way or move towards the right here as we burn more towards the ground.
Oh, that looks insane!
Maybe it's different now.
Let me try a crew report.
Hey, look at this!
While in space near Minmus, jetpacking down there would probably be fun.
You doubt you could get back up, though.
Right.
I'll take that experiment.
What about a...
I forgot about EVA reports.
Also, did I bring thingies?
Let me see.
Inventory.
Oh my god, I did!
Let's see.
Inventory.
Let's conduct science experiments.
EVA report.
Oh my god, we're getting...
We're gonna get so much science from this mission.
The mesmerizing aquamarine flats almost make you forget to keep one hand on the ship's handle.
I mean, we're not attached to the ship anymore.
Let's do this one.
Oh wait, how does that work?
Oh yeah.
Okay, it's the same thing as last time.
It's cool though.
I dig it.
That's 60 science!
Watching the astronaut look through the EVA science kit has given us conclusive evidence.
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
Listen.
You know what?
We're not...
We're actually not even that interested in science anymore.
This is mostly about money now.
So, it's contracts.
That's what it is.
All we care about.
Maybe we can do a mystery goo thingy as well.
Let's see what that says.
Okay, 5.5 is not bad.
The goo sticks to the Minmus side of the container and appears to be attracted to the tiny moon.
You wonder if the goo is hungry too.
What is this goo anyway?
Is it just chewing gum or something?
Collect that data.
Restore it.
I'm gonna put the data in the little capsule over here.
Where is it?
There it is.
Store.
We have five experiments in there right now.
Not bad, eh?
Yo, I wonder if I could land on Minmus with just my jetpack.
Because look at our orbit.
We're at 90 meters per second.
It's like nothing.
I mean, obviously, we're gonna speed up as we approach the surface, but imagine.
Anything else I should be doing?
Maybe we take some measurements here.
Get back inside the vessel first.
And then we're gonna do temperature stuff.
But I think we already took these.
Yeah.
What about that one?
Also nothing.
Yeah, okay.
Fine.
Crew report?
Oh, we already have that.
Huh.
Uh, oh.
Extend the legs.
Wait, spring, damper, auto?
Oh, cool.
I'll just leave it on auto, I guess, for now.
You can adjust how powerful the string is.
Hey, look at the little thing in the distance there.
Rotating.
Uh, just auto.
Yeah.
Okay, we should start burning a little bit now.
How are we doing on battery?
Oh, man.
We're just...
Is it because this one has the alternator?
It does.
Beautiful.
Actually, we're gonna get more, uh...
It's gonna be more efficient if we burn close to the surface.
I'm just gonna speed up a little bit here.
What is our trajectory looking like?
That's not great.
It's because the moon is rotating.
I forgot about that part.
See?
Now we're going straight down.
Well, pretty much straight down.
And the moon is still rotating.
Ah, this is actually annoying.
Stop rotating.
Cargill.
Cannot warp faster than 1x while below 3,000.
Interesting.
Oh, let me also do this.
Wait, am I crazy?
That doesn't change anything.
Maybe it's because there's no water on this.
That's probably why.
Whoa, it's gonna be right on the border here.
If we hit the edge, it's gonna be a little problematic.
I am ready to just take off again and shit hits the fan, you know?
If shit hits the fan.
God, this looks so...
I gotta take away the UI, man.
I gotta look at this.
Look at the shadow down there!
Burn slightly.
Speed up a bit more.
500 meters.
This looks pretty damn flat!
The first flat landing...
Please don't crack whatever this is.
It looks brittle.
I doubt that's a thing, but, you know, who knows?
100 meters.
Slow down just a bit.
I'm actually just keep it like that now.
Fucking butter.
Garlic butter.
God, that's beautiful.
Wow, look at this place!
Okay, material study.
Show me what we got.
75!
While the material samples were processed, you began to turn your thoughts to how much Minmus looks like a mint dessert and have discovered that you are now hungry.
Nah, man.
It's not a mint dessert.
It's...
It's a sour piece of candy.
Okay.
Transfer that.
Oh, my God.
This is an alien world.
I mean, look at this.
This looks so alien, doesn't it?
We got the mystery goo.
This is for the contract?
The goo begins to resemble a particularly delicious bowl of rocky minty ice cream you had once.
You slap yourself out of it.
Did we do it now?
Wait, hold on.
Collect it.
Zero percent of 50 percent.
Wait a minute.
Are they telling me I need to somehow deploy this on the surface?
How the hell?
Wait, I don't know how to do that.
Okay, I misunderstood.
This is not...
Oh, shit.
Hey, at least we're getting some science, right?
Damn, 36 just for this?
From Minmus' great flats.
Collected and recorded atmospheric pressure data from the surroundings.
Lovely.
What about the temperatures?
The ground seems to reflect most of the sun's thermal energy.
Yet the ground temperature is much higher than it should be.
This warrants further investigation.
Hmm.
Maybe there's some activity going on below here.
Maybe there's actually liquid whatever the liquid is down below here, you know?
Liquid mint?
Ha ha.
Um, crew report?
Overwrite?
No!
Wait, I have an idea.
Why don't I just take Bob?
Right?
I'm going to...
take data.
Crew report while in space near Minmus added.
I'm gonna take that, and I'm gonna bring it to the container.
What?
Yeah.
Oh, God.
Whoa, the gravity is really low.
Look at this.
Wow.
There's nothing.
It's almost like an asteroid.
This is almost like being in space.
I mean, I guess we are in space, but you know what I mean.
There we go, it's been stored, so now I go back in.
Oh, wait, we do EVA report?
Just above Minmus' Great Flats.
If the spaceship fails, you could probably use the jetpack to get back into orbit.
Yeah.
You probably could.
Gravity here is insanely low.
Let me see here.
We're gonna reset this guy as well.
Restore.
Or, I guess, restore, not reset.
I think we took this measurement up in the air.
We haven't taken it a while down here yet.
Let me go to the surface here.
Oh, my God.
Oh, look at that Black Horizon.
That's eerie.
Oh, look at that up there.
We got Kerbin, we got the moon, and some other planet in the distance.
What is that?
Dres.
Okay.
Wow.
Jeez.
Kind of want to lick the surface of this.
Dang, son.
Can we do golf?
Wait.
Oops.
EVA science.
Come on.
Watching the astronaut look through the EVA science kit.
Yeah, okay.
This is not gonna change, is it?
As the ball arcs off into the distance, you observe the ballet of physics between the applied impulse and the body's gravity.
our scientists will rejoice at the results and hopefully agree that the six iron was great club selection.
I know enough about golf to know that that is a type of club.
That's right, I know.
Now we plant a flag.
Oh, man.
What should we call this?
Let's call it Alien World.
Because that is exactly what this is.
It is unbelievably alien.
the textures are something that we've never seen before.
The smell is like that of a fart.
Oh.
Space suit.
Look at that.
God, this has to be like...
I think this is the prettiest sort of body outside of carbon that I've found so far.
Damn.
This is just pure cinema.
EVA report.
Oh, we already did that.
Okay.
Okay, so we did all that.
Take off here.
God, this is just...
Ho, ho, ho!
This game is amazing, dude.
Come on, buddy.
Grab that.
Okay, I think we should let Cargill also explore the surface a bit.
Maybe we can double dip on the EVA report.
Think about it.
She's not gonna be left out of this.
No way.
Wait, I wonder if I can edit the flag thing.
Whoa!
Oh, don't crash into the flag.
Wait, what?
Uh, read flag.
Oh, that's so cool, man.
Look at that.
I guess Cargill is, like, disgusted with Bob right now.
She's like, God damn it, Bob.
Come on.
Take it serious, will you?
We're doing science here.
Unbelievable.
Dude, we get so high just from jumping.
That's crazy.
Okay, so check it out.
What we're gonna do now, I'm gonna click on this, get even more material study.
Oh, we can't do that.
Okay, we need a we need a Bob.
Shit.
Or I guess we just do it from inside the craft.
Let me see if I can double dip on the EVA report.
I probably should do it down here, then.
Because the other one I had from the space...
I can plant another flag!
You know what?
Let's do it.
Right here.
Cargill deserves her own flag, too.
Alien world...
2.
Disregard...
the other flag.
Classic Bob behavior.
This...
is fascinating.
Oh, yeah.
Good job, Cargill.
Alright, take me up again.
It's time to get out of here.
Well, it is fun to explore.
We do gotta get home.
Grab that.
Let me see if we actually did do this thing.
No, we didn't.
That's great.
Oh, wait.
Moonstone.
No, what was it?
Green sandstone.
Okay, hold on.
There's actually not that many stones here.
Maybe we can find one.
Wait a minute.
We're not going home yet.
Let's see if we can do this.
I do still have a suspicion that we are gonna need the surface sample thingy.
Material study.
The low temperature has frozen one of the liquid samples into a sort of iced cream.
Was it green before?
I mean, if it's goo, it has to be green, right?
It cannot be any other color.
That's just a law.
Transfer.
There we go.
What about the...
Wait, same...
vessel interaction?
Autostrut.
I think this is something I may have enabled by doing advanced tweakables.
I'm not sure what that means.
Aim camera.
Oh!
Oh, that's nice!
I actually really like that.
Pretty cool.
Configure vessel naming.
Oh, you can rename it right now!
Oh, you can even give it like a...
Oh, this is a lander!
That's amazing!
What about the mystery goo?
Did we already do this?
The goo starts to bounce slowly from top to bottom.
I think we just did this, didn't we?
Transfer data.
Let's see if it says okay for this.
Oh, okay.
We can't.
That's fine.
Bob, you're going out again.
I need you to reset the science canister.
Come on, Bob.
Collect the data, I guess.
Restore.
Get back in the vessel.
Time to find a rock.
Okay.
Uh...
So how do we do this?
Um...
I guess we want to be going that way.
I'm going to sort of go towards orbit right now.
But I'm going to see if I can't land somewhere else.
So see if I can't find a little rock.
I mean, there's rocks up there, but that's very far away.
Let's see what happens.
Okay, lift.
Oh, we don't have that much fuel.
I gotta be a little careful here.
Go.
Okay, so it's going that way.
Got it.
Okay.
Well, we don't need a...
like, we're already fucking flying.
Look at that.
But do I really want to land on this?
It's way too hilly.
It's not good.
220 electric charge.
We do have to keep an eye on that, too.
You know?
Uh, wait.
I'm going the wrong way now.
Oh, shit.
Okay, you know what?
Fuck it.
We're going home.
We gotta play save with this fuel.
I gotta go, man.
Unless we try and land on top of that.
Yo, it looks flat!
Look at that!
Wait, does it say...
We're gonna try and land there.
It looks very flat.
We can't speed up time.
We need to be above 3,000?
What was it?
Yeah.
There we go.
Oh, that's almost too perfect?
Damn.
Look at that!
Dude!
Tell me there's rocks up here I can grab.
I see rocks!
Battery?
Tooth?
Oh, wait.
I guess we're gaining battery every time we burn this engine.
That's amazing.
We really gotta keep an eye out on our fuel, though.
imagine getting stuck here.
The flags back there.
Gonna start burning when we're very close just to save as much fuel as possible.
I love that you can...
So, the shadow is actually so helpful, because when these two connect, it's a better indicator for me, at least, how close we are.
Oh, man, this is freaking picture-perfect.
Butter!
There's a lot of stones here!
It's gotta be Bob, though, right?
If anything.
He's the scientist.
Maybe it'll...
Let's say a fine one.
Maybe it'll say, ah, you need the upgrade, you know, to do the thing.
Actually, why would I...
Why would I ever walk when I can just jetpack over there, right?
So they called it a green sandstone?
Minmus's midlands.
You've confirmed that the surface does not taste like mint ice cream.
Bob!
Did you taste the...
Did you taste the moon?
Be honest with me.
Wait a minute, are we getting, like, a whole new set of signs, then?
Because it's a different, uh, place?
Wait.
We gotta play some golf.
Dude, are we not gonna come home with, like, unspeakable amounts of signs?
This is gonna be insane.
I wish he did the hammer and feather test.
Ah, you missed completely, Bob.
God damn it.
Oh.
Yeah, take it.
That was a lot of signs.
So it doesn't seem like I can click on any of these rocks.
Like, what are we missing here?
Maybe the prop won't even pop up, you know, unless I have that upgrade.
Or I need to be close, and then I right-click myself.
And then the thing pops up, maybe.
Let me try something.
A sandstone.
So, sand would be...
I mean, you find that near water, right?
Or liquids.
So maybe it would make more sense to...
Oh, my God.
Maybe we should have actually explored the beach, so to speak, near the frozen lake we were at.
Maybe that's where they would be, you know?
All these look the same.
Yeah, I think...
I think...
Wait.
It can't be one of these big...
Oh, my God.
I'm going fast.
Look at this.
Whoa!
Meanwhile...
Wait.
Bob is just looking at me.
No, sorry.
What was his name?
Cargill?
He's looking at me going through the window going, what is Bob doing?
This jackass.
Oh, shit.
Okay, I gotta go deal with the clothes in a second here.
What about this big boy?
Can I put this in my pocket?
Oh, you know what it is?
It probably...
Oh.
Hold on.
Space center.
We need to see...
It's probably gonna tell me which areas it is present in.
The Great Flats...
Greater Flats or Flats Biomes?
Wait.
Great...
Fuck.
Isn't that where I was?
I was right.
It was...
It was somewhere around there.
God damn it.
Bob.
I'm gonna fly you.
Apparently.
I guess I am since I'm jetpacking.
Unpacking jets.
Okay, uh...
Whatever.
Let's get back to the ship.
Now, we may actually have enough fuel to go back again.
But maybe that's a little crazy.
Whoa.
Careful now.
I wonder if you can die by just smashing into something at horizontal speed.
I'm not gonna try or test that hypothesis right now.
Imagine your visor breaks out here.
That's a horror story.
Wait, what?
Experiments you have collected cannot be stored on the Mark II command pod.
Are you sure you want to continue?
No.
Wait, what?
Maybe.
What?
Oh, wait.
I missed the message.
I don't know what I did.
Uh, crew report.
We tried jumping into the air and strafing at the same time.
Now, if only you had a water pistol.
We do have a butt.
And gas.
Lock temperature.
Override?
No, no, no, no, no.
I need to transfer them.
There.
Conduct study.
I'm gonna grab transfer.
Yes.
Transfer that over there.
And then transfer that one.
there.
And now Bob should be able to reset these.
And everything should be great.
Dude, having a scientist on these missions is nuts.
Why does it say collect data?
I already transferred.
Reset.
Okay, weird.
Oh, shit.
Bob?
Oh, I thought maybe we ran out of fuel.
Imagine.
Imagine rotating, running out of fuel, and just smashing into the floor.
Well, when I say smash, it's like very slowly, I guess.
Oh, my God.
Bob!
Wow, what a flip!
Fucking 10 out of 10 on that one.
That was beautiful.
Wow.
Bob can do it all, it seems.
Let's go reset the goo thingy.
There you go.
Back inside.
Oh, my God.
Now what?
Let's do this one.
It's kind of hard to keep track of this.
I'm just gathering a bunch of shit right now.
I don't know if I did these already.
I'm gonna do it anyway.
We're gonna try and transfer it over to the thingy.
Oh, this one already did.
Okay, okay.
So this one goes there.
This one goes there.
Oh, wait.
Media removed module inoperable?
I don't know what's happening, dude.
I mean, how much do I have in there?
13!
I guess that's how to keep track of it.
But this one we already did, right?
So if I try to transfer this, it's gotta say override or something.
Yeah, okay.
So we can't do that.
Makes sense.
We don't want to overwrite that.
Okay, let's just get out of here, man.
Honestly, fuck this sandstone.
We're not gonna find it.
It's over.
We're going home.
Retract these.
That's right.
Oh, I love the little icon now.
So good.
Okay.
I think I'm gonna burn up here.
It's actually kind of harder to see my vessel now that it's a different icon.
I'm gonna get up here.
And right there.
Now we burn prograde.
Battery?
Great.
In fact, we're gonna get more now when we burn.
And this seemed to be a pretty good setup here.
I liked it.
show me the Perry.
Show me Katy Perry.
Absis.
Oh, wait.
No, it's Apo-Absis I'm looking for.
What am I saying?
Oh, wait.
What's happening?
We got issues?
Test, test.
Are we good?
Oh, fuck.
Laundry.
You're right.
Thank you.
Okay, you know what?
I'm gonna do this.
We're in stable orbit now.
So you get to
you get to sort of enjoy this view while I'm gone.
Okay?
I'll be back in a sec.
We're back.
It's time for the return trip.
Ah, man.
God, this game is just fucking feeling, isn't it?
I feel it in my heart, man.
Okay.
It's time to go back.
Where's home?
There it is.
Okay, so we're gonna do a maneuver node here.
I think the best place to do it is like here.
So that our escape happens on this side.
Not bad.
Dude, 58 kilometers?
There's no way.
Oh, wait.
It's 58,000.
I was like, there's no way we hit it that well.
Okay, there's actually a better option here, too.
That's not that great.
But I like this, where perhaps this is sort of close.
So this is a good one.
Let's point.
So we're gonna burn in one hour and 47 minutes.
And guys, I'm not gonna fast...
We're gonna sit here for an hour and 45 minutes.
This is just immersion.
I'm kidding.
We're not gonna do that.
Fast forward.
There we are.
In one minute.
You ready?
It's time to go home with all the science.
Carson.
I mean, Cargill.
And Bob.
Are you ready?
We're gonna burn in exactly 10-ish seconds.
We're gonna burn now.
Stop.
And we are on a great trajectory here.
Let's leave the Sphere of Influence.
Now we burn Retrograde.
What a mission.
Come on.
There we go.
Retro.
Battery.
More than fine.
Periapsis.
21 million miles.
Actually, it's probably 21,000 million miles, which is 21 gigamiles.
It's a lot of miles.
Boom.
We're actually on an intercept course.
So I don't know if that's good.
It's probably bad.
So I'm gonna prograde a little bit more.
Prograde until we are at like 30,000 meters.
That's like my go-to nowadays.
Okay, so...
slowly.
Boom.
36.
Not bad.
We're gonna get there and then before we actually enter the atmosphere, I'm gonna burn even more retro.
Speed up.
Oh, you know what I should do?
Check this out.
I just figured out a genius way to operate here.
I'm gonna go to here.
Add a maneuver.
Do something like that.
And then I'm just gonna fast forward to it.
Oh, or I could just say warp here, I guess.
Wait, that's probably better.
Even better.
Warp here.
That's Carson, by the way, who is speeding around the planet.
Man, it's taking a while.
I'm coming in.
Please slow down in time.
Oh!
Okay.
It does it automatically.
I had my faith.
I think we're good.
Okay.
Now we point retro.
We're coming in at 3.0.
So this is actually dangerous now.
Last time it was not super easy to control.
When we had this system here.
um, I'm just gonna start burning, bro.
I'm gonna slow down a little bit here.
In fact, I'll use all my fuel.
Let's see if this is a good idea.
We're gonna come down at a steeper angle, but I think it's okay.
Done.
Alright, cargo, hit the switch.
In 3, 2, 1,
lock-in.
Heat shield confirmed is present.
Battery is fully charged.
And the mood is at an all-time high.
No, I don't want to overwrite that, actually.
Here we go, here we go.
Oh, I'm so nervous always, especially with this sort of, you know, in front.
I'm keeping an eye on that retrograde indicator there.
As soon as that starts to wobble out, I'm gonna take over.
Well, we should be okay here.
Oh no, it's starting to move.
Okay, just calmly, calmly make corrections.
It really wants to turn over.
Oh, oh shit!
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
I'm not sure if this is stable or not.
I'm just, I'm holding the button right now.
It's definitely not good.
But we are slowing down.
Okay, we're fine, we're fine, we're fine.
Crap.
Oh, we're totally chilling.
We're chilling!
No problem.
Fuck yeah.
Imagine if we died here, man.
Losing all that science and two of our top people.
That would be a proper disaster.
Shoots!
Drogues are out!
Speed up a bit.
Coming down near the grassland it seems.
We're gonna deploy the drogues, no, the main chutes.
And these ones have been...
Also, I thought about something.
Like, I was about to say, let's try and just get rid of these because you can cut them off, you know?
So that we go down even faster.
But since we have this down at the bottom, I'm not actually sure it's gonna be good.
Could be a bad idea.
Not entirely sure.
Are we landing on that ravine?
Or cliff?
Nah, we're fine.
Whoops!
And again, I ask the question,
where did I see it?
Oh, there.
Look at that!
What is that?
I need to know what that is.
Can we see it from here?
Nope.
That's actually looking straight up.
And now we have it set to surface.
If I put that...
Yeah, see?
Sea level is much, uh, much lower than this.
Here we go.
What happened?
Oh, wait, did the heat shield get destroyed?
Oh my god, bro!
I'm just glad we're fine.
Holy crap.
Maybe we need more parachute next time.
We have 660 fucking science, bro!
What the hell?
Damn!
Wow!
Whoa!
Bob is level two now.
Cargill also gained exp...
It's also level two.
Yo!
Wait, can I...
Oh, it's not enough yet.
We need this upgrade.
A-S-A-P.
Especially because then we can get surface samples.
I need contracts.
Explore Eve?
I don't know what Eve is!
I guess it's a planet or moon or something.
In the grand scheme of things, we know very little about Eve.
Let's see if we can explore it a bit further.
Yeah.
I mean, I...
I feel like I need to get that money first, you know?
I'm kind of mad about this.
We want you to send us science data from the surface of Minmus.
I don't understand what this means.
This is just flavor.
There's nothing actually telling me here how to do this.
Build a new orbital station around Kirby.
What, my old one was not good enough?
What's going to give me a lot of money?
Hey, we get an advance of 130,000 for this one.
Is it time to just take a bunch of contracts to get the money?
This one is a good amount of money, too.
And that's rescuing someone around in low Minmus orbit.
That's kind of exciting.
And we get another Kerbal back.
I wonder, though.
So, you know what would be really cool?
And I don't know if this is a thing.
But let's say I go rescue someone who is, you know, in orbit around Minmus, like this one says I should.
Maybe that Kerbal will already be level one or level two or something when I get them.
I would love that.
I don't remember if that was the case with the other ones we got back from Kerbin.
I'm not sure.
So, hold on.
We needed 900-something thousand for the upgrade, so this is going to give us, it's like 800-something thousand.
This is an advance of 43.
There's no advance on this one?
I mean, this one we're going to get.
If we're going to go...
wait a sec.
I'm going to take this so we get the advance.
And obviously I want to do it too.
Today's your lucky day.
Simply head to even pass by it.
Easy as pie.
No risk at all.
Now sign this waiver.
Okay, so that's just a flyby.
How hard can it be?
Right?
Sometimes science throws you a curveball.
Okay, whatever.
We've read that before.
I will take it.
That's 811,000 now?
Let's take this one as well and actually do it.
There we go.
We're going to rescue you from...
Oh, science data from surface of Minmus.
Where was this one?
I needed it before.
Science data from space around Minmus.
This is an easy one.
I will take that.
We're not going to have enough from these advances, unfortunately.
But maybe I can extract some money via this.
Fundraising campaign?
Takes reputation gains and yields funds.
What is reputation even good for?
I don't understand that.
Hey, maybe I can trade some science for some money.
I have so much science.
I never thought I would say this, but here we are.
Research rights sellout?
Wait, wait, 4,000 only for a hundred science?
Wait, this is terrible.
This is horrible.
These trades are not good.
It's like that meme, you know, with the guy with his hands together like Mr. Burns from The Simpsons, saying, alert, trade offer, you know?
You get, I receive, and it's just not fair at all.
Well, shit.
Uh, I guess I can take this.
No, wait, I have full contracts now.
Damn.
Oh, my God, I need this money.
I need this money.
Maybe we do this.
Wait, patents licensing?
Takes 5% science gains from contracts.
Yields funds for each one unit of science.
Now, this is absolutely terrible.
Horrible.
Okay, let's go rescue a guy.
And then we're gonna get the money, and we should be okay.
So, we're gonna take the, I guess, the crew, but it's gonna be an advanced version of the crew.
The Min, Min was nasty contract.
Oh, that's the space station we have to make as well.
Right.
That is a nasty contract.
Um, what did I just use?
Oh, the MSV.
What a beaut.
This is such a beauty.
We can change this slightly.
MSV.
This is gonna be the Minmus rescue vessel.
This is the MRV.
We shall go there and collect the Kerbal.
Bomb.
MRV.
Okay.
So, we don't need this shit anymore.
Get rid of it.
And honestly, maybe we say goodbye to this crap.
I actually I hate it.
I'm not a fan.
We can do crew report in space.
It's cool.
We're chilling.
And this, I feel way better about this setup here when we come back.
You know, it's just much better.
Looks cooler too.
We can even land if we want to.
And I think we want to.
This is a great rocket, man.
This is such a...
Oh my god.
I just want to make love to this rocket.
Not really, but you know what I mean.
I'm happy about it.
I'm excited.
Okay, so.
We have a contract to go rescue the guy.
And the green sandstone.
Maybe it's going to happen if we decide to land.
We'll see.
Transmit or that's from space around.
And then we need to go
save Looney Kerman.
Okay.
And fly by Eve.
Gather scientific data from Eve and return.
Maybe I should figure out where Eve is as well.
But let's take off, shall we?
So these two...
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
If we're going to rescue someone, we need to leave a room for someone.
Cargill, you're up.
Also, what can you do now?
Prograde, retrograde, radial, full vessel, control.
Ah, whatever.
I'm happy.
Oh, wait.
One problem that we have right now is I don't have a battery with me now.
But we do have the alternator, so I think we're fine.
Yeah, never mind.
We have the alternator.
We're chilling.
Let's do it.
The Merv.
Oh, wait.
I...
Wait.
I misspelled.
There we go.
Minimus rescue vessel.
Merv.
We're taking off.
And...
A three.
And a two.
Assume out a lot.
And a one.
Lift off of the Merv in search of Lwenny.
Lwenny?
I'm gonna call him Lenny.
If it is a he.
Maybe it's not.
I don't know.
Cargill, you're on your own this time.
How does it feel?
Good.
Okay, well, I was worried you would be kind of scared.
Oh.
Fantastic.
We're doing it.
I'm gonna start turning in three seconds.
There we go.
Why does it want to rotate?
I don't understand.
It feels less responsive than when I had the science module on it.
Come on, rotate back, please.
It's also time to disengage these boosters in a second here.
Bye-bye.
See ya, buddy.
So now we look at Apoapsis.
In fact, I'm gonna keep it on this angle for a bit before I move further.
50.
Dude, I'm getting pretty good at orbiting here.
I do have a dream of getting to orbit with this stage right here.
Maybe now that we dropped some mass, we can do it.
I think we can do it.
In fact, what if I just start turning now?
Is that crazy?
Maybe I'm a crazy boy for doing this.
This may be insane.
I'm trying something new.
Okay, Apoapsis is kind of stable right now.
Obviously, we're still kind of deep in the atmosphere, so that's gonna be more air resistance while we're burning right now.
but still.
Okay, we're starting to decrease...
Actually, I'm happy about decreasing Apoapsis.
500.
Nah, it's not gonna be enough.
I mean, it's gonna be the same every time.
I haven't even looked at the map yet.
Okay, next stage.
See ya!
Dude, this is perfect!
This may be the best orbit I've done.
Look at the Apoapsis and Periapsis.
This is...
a fucking beautiful orbit!
Wow!
Cargill, you're so good!
And look how tiny this little guy is.
Wait, what were we doing again?
Oh yeah, we need to rescue someone.
Uh, maybe we should figure out where exactly he is.
Lenny.
Hey, I like that he's on the equator.
That's gonna make it a little easier for me.
All right.
Let's, uh, set sail for Minmus.
First, that.
Zoom out.
Select Minmus.
Target.
So it's gonna be around there.
Ah, but wait!
Ah, fucking inclination.
Shit.
Uh, we're gonna have to do it at the ascending node.
And we have to go down at the ascending node to flip this disk.
Mmm.
Get rid of...
Wait, what?
Oh, okay, right.
So put it there.
And we're going down.
Also, there was a way...
How was it again?
Right, click.
There we go.
But I need to adjust...
Ah, shit.
Bro, I'm not a...
How did I see that number last time when I...
Oh, there it is.
Now it appeared.
0.1.
0.0.
Okay.
It's also more maneuverable now that we have less mass.
Oh, yeah!
I forget that we have the actual ascending node symbols too here.
Sweet.
Now we're gonna...
I'm actually just gonna fast forward to that.
And do it automatically.
Oof.
On the dark side.
Okay.
So we burn in 55 seconds.
What is this down here?
Percentage of the burns delta V used to calculate the start burn value?
Wait, what?
Percentage of the delta V used to calculate the...
That...
I don't understand that.
That is gibberish to me.
I'm gonna burn here.
Now.
7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Okay.
And now we need to be heading in...
this direction.
This is getting to be routine here.
How did Lenny get stranded over there anyway, huh?
That's what I wanna know.
We got something good there.
Bro, that is...
That is beautiful.
That is wonderful.
Wow.
Perfect.
Get ready to burn.
Okay, fast forward.
Angle it precisely here.
Aww.
You're all alone, Carl.
It was nice to see Bob sitting next to you, huh?
But you're gonna have someone else.
You're gonna make a new friend on this trip.
And you're gonna love it.
I hear Lenny is, uh...
quite a guy.
Or gal.
Burning.
This is a longer burn.
Guys, this game might be a masterpiece.
Not even kidding.
Like, this...
Okay, I'm also biased.
Okay, I love space.
I love all this sort of shit.
But still, I mean...
The progression is just top-notch.
It's...
Chef's kiss, you know?
Angle it a little more this way.
Okay, get ready now.
If I can time this precisely.
Four, three, two, one.
Let's see what we got.
Onset target.
That's beautiful.
In fact, that kind of looks like...
Yeah, that's great.
So I'm actually just gonna use this functionality again where I...
warp to...
here.
Lenny, I'm coming!
I was about to say, maybe we should have brought some RCS for this.
But, uh...
Nah.
Too late now, anyway.
It is nice to have that little extra fine control, you know?
Would be nice practice, too.
Oopsy-daisy!
Oh, shit.
Okay, it stopped automatically.
I don't know why I did that.
That was funny.
Okay, we're here.
Uh...
Maneuver.
Obviously, we gotta do this.
Whoa.
Wait a minute.
Where are you?
Lenny?
Dude, he's very close to the surface.
What the hell?
Dang, son.
Alright.
Wait a sec.
What's going on here?
Oh!
Right, I'm moving this way because I came in at a weird angle where I was in front of Minmus.
And then the Minmus is passing...
The Minmus is passing me by.
So I'm gonna end up behind it when I escape, right?
Makes sense.
That's too much.
So he was at...
Let me see.
Seven kilometers!
Is he gonna get a haircut from one of those mountains?
That's kind of scary.
Three.
So I guess I'll go to...
Ten.
Ten seems good.
Also, the inclination is not perfect here, but that's okay.
We can fix that in post.
Okay.
Warp to the burn.
That's Kerbin.
Oh, it's right there.
The one thing I don't like about this capsule that I have here, the visibility out the window, man.
It's non-existent.
You know?
The one-man capsule is much better in that way.
You actually get to look out the window and admire.
Not so much here.
Okay, let's start rotating.
I'm gonna rotate this way.
Honestly, it doesn't really matter if we wait 30 seconds here.
We don't even need this, honestly.
It's just gonna confuse me.
So we agreed on, like, ten.
Oh my god, I nailed it!
Ten!
Ha ha!
I hit it precisely.
Okay.
Now?
We speed up a bit.
Lenny, I'm coming.
Very slowly.
Holy.
Wow.
He's doing a lot of laps there before I arrive.
Hey, maybe we're gonna be kinda close to each other when it happens.
Imagine.
Wait.
Ah, no way, right?
He's too fast.
Oh, he's so fast.
But I plan to be in...
Also, when we reach the ascending node here, we need to adjust our inclination.
Otherwise, we're on no chance of catching this dude.
He quick!
Now please show me the number if you don't mind.
God, it's so janky, dude.
Why is the number not showing?
Ah!
Whatever.
I swear to god.
Why is this number not showing?
Okay, now right-click, and then...
It's the number down here, damn it!
I'm losing my mind.
I'm just gonna...
Wait,
why is that...
Oh, I guess we're adding a velocity component along prograde as well by doing this technically.
Because if you imagine this being a vector, right?
it has a downwards component and a component that way.
So we're actually speeding up enough to reach escape at that point.
So really, we want to add a bit of this as well.
I'm just gonna fucking eyeball it, because apparently this number doesn't want to show up!
Okay, that looks about right.
And then...
Retro.
Let's see if we can't get a good intersect already.
Nah.
Actually, we should not be doing that.
I should start by having this.
I wish the number would show up.
Just start by burning that.
So in 30 seconds.
This is kind of a precise burn.
So we gotta be on our toes.
Good.
And now when we reach periapsis...
Ah, wait.
We're actually...
I was hoping we would be a little higher in elevation.
But I guess it's fine.
Gonna burn retro when we reach periapsis.
And then I'm just gonna leave it a little higher.
So like, right here.
Like that.
That's maybe a bit too...
It's gonna take forever, isn't it?
I guess I can also extend it on the other side.
I don't know if anything I'm saying is making sense to you right now.
I'm kinda, you know, speaking gibberish a little bit, I guess.
Because I'm trying to think at the same time.
Okay, now.
We wanna burn prograde, actually.
Just to get that periapsis up a little more.
There we go.
Actually, maybe we'll give it slightly more, just so we don't have to wait an eternity.
Like that.
What about battery?
Ah, we're totally good.
Perfect.
And now we just kinda wait.
He's gonna catch up to us at some point and then we do another burn.
Here he comes.
Let's see if we can do something here now.
Nah, it's maybe a little
shit.
I waited too long.
There's no way I can catch him with this, right?
I waited too much.
Oops.
Ah, we actually got a good one there.
Oof!
That's a pretty good one.
Okay, we take that.
Oh, burn in seven seconds!
I can't turn it fast enough.
Two.
One.
Zero.
Burn!
That was way too much, wasn't it?
Shit.
Let me try again.
There we go.
I just need a little more head start, please.
Give me, like, a warning.
Okay, so 30 seconds now.
That's good.
Let's point in the right direction.
Also, wait a sec.
Yeah, I mean...
Hmm.
It's only six meters per second.
This is, like, I need to be very, very conservative here.
not bad.
We take that.
He's gonna overtake us here, and then we're gonna speed up.
And then we're gonna overtake him.
Oh, shit!
Guys, we assumed that the body of the moon is transparent and, uh, traversable.
It isn't.
It's not.
Ha ha, fuck me.
Ah, the math is not mathing.
Maybe we have a better one.
Let's see.
I mean, we got a...
Not good.
Honestly, that's not too bad.
One minute.
We have plenty of fuel.
We're chilling here.
And every time we burn, we get electric charge or EC.
6.6 again.
The same amount.
Okay, here we go.
Lenny's not, uh, making it easy for me here.
Playing hard to get.
So, at this intersect, we're at 20 kilometers.
Honestly, I think we can...
That's a fine intersect for me, honestly.
I dig it.
We're using that.
Actually, this is 8...
Wait, this was 18...
Yeah, this is a fine enough intersect.
Actually, it's not.
Actually, it is.
Is it?
Maybe...
I need to...
I need to test something with this.
Let me quickly see here.
If I...
If I do this...
So, he's gonna be faster than us, which means we gotta slow down.
Tell me we can meet a little.
We cannot.
Fuck it, we're doing it live.
Where are you?
There you are.
This is insane, probably, but...
Hear me out.
Let's see here.
He is...
currently...
He's moving faster than us.
Okay, so we gotta move towards him.
But are we not just gonna...
We may have a planet in the way here.
This is the problem.
Are we on an intersect with the planet right now?
Not really.
Okay, we're approaching.
In fact, I'm gonna go faster.
Because I'm just a baller like that.
Maybe it's time to turn around now.
This is some crazy maneuvering here.
See, right now, it's kind of looking like we may...
Not bad.
I actually like it.
In fact, I'm gonna align it even better.
Like that.
0.6 kilometers.
Beautiful.
And then when we get there, we're gonna start to drift past each other, so I gotta react fast.
In fact, I can just start slowing down right before we cross paths here.
Go a little faster.
Okay.
We gotta start slowing down.
Come on.
Right on the money.
50 meters per second.
Moving closer.
There we go.
We can make it better.
And now we need to really slow down.
Yes, yes.
12.
Even more, even more.
There we go.
Lenny.
God damn it.
Okay.
Your name is not Lenny then.
It's Luna.
Let's do it.
I've come for you.
I've come to take you home.
There we go.
Oh.
Beautiful.
Both are inside.
And look at that.
A sunrise on Minmus.
We also cannot forget that we need to take science around the space.
Around Minmus.
Crew report.
Here we are.
The giant mint in space.
It's zero science, but I'm taking it anyway.
Let's see if...
Oh, Lenny's a scientist.
I mean, Luna.
Luna, you're gonna have to do an EVA report?
No.
It's also zero.
Whatever.
It's fine.
There's nothing else we can do, right?
I guess there's this one.
Uh...
Luna?
You're gonna play around with the little toy I brought.
Uh...
Let me see your inventory.
Nice.
And now we do some science.
It's probably gonna net us a little bit.
I just wanna make sure that we do this contract.
Nah, not really.
Okay.
Whatever.
All right, get in.
I guess I sucked this place dry of science, huh?
Oh, I just...
I just affected the...
Uh...
What do you call it?
The stability of the vessel there by bumping into it like that.
I thought we were quite heavy, but apparently not that heavy.
And I guess, uh...
You know...
What's it called?
The physical concept behind rotation and you hit one at the end.
There's a word for that in English.
You know, you can apply more force at the ends, basically.
There's a word.
Anyway!
Time to head home.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Also, wait.
Uh...
Let me see here.
Bring a...
Space around Minimus.
Wasn't there more I had?
Uh...
This one we've done.
Yeah.
Okay.
Time to go home.
Which means we burn here.
Warping there.
Let's look at the surface while we go.
Oh my god.
We're speeding!
Looks so crazy when you're in a time warp here.
Oh my god.
It looks like we're about to hit the surface!
Crazy.
But I know we're not because if Luna was in orbit around here so many times and we matched her orbit, there's no way we're gonna crash into anything.
Right?
It makes sense.
Retrograde.
No!
Prograde!
You didn't see that, Luna.
Cargill is usually very professional.
This was a minor mishap.
She knows all about Prograde.
And burn.
Ah, good enough!
I'll take that.
Come on.
I wonder if we're gonna have enough money when we come home to upgrade the Science Center.
That would be incredible.
time we burn Retrograde here.
Are you excited, Luna?
I think she is.
Oh, that's a bit too much.
Prograde.
Wasn't paying attention.
Burn opposite.
Take it to 30 again, I guess.
It's like my standard, you know?
And then we're gonna perform the maneuver of warping directly to Kerbin.
Warp here.
But when you do it like that, it's kinda slow.
But I guess it's safe.
Remember that one time where I accidentally hit too many time warps and it fuckin' almost flung me straight into the planet?
That was scary.
Ah, we're gonna be on the dark side?
I don't like that.
Okay, I'm gonna spend my fuel here so that's not the case.
Me no likey.
Ah, but wait!
It's too late for that now.
Yeah, fuck it.
I guess we're landing on the dark side.
Shit.
Should've thought about that earlier.
Unless...
Unless I don't burn and I just let the atmosphere take care of it.
Maybe we land over here then.
I believe.
In fact, I believe so hard I'm gonna disengage this.
Goodbye.
Oh, and re-entry is gonna be so much more comfortable now that we don't have this ugly-ass little attachment.
Okay.
Put on your hats of courage because it's time for re-entry.
Look at Apwaps.
It's just falling down.
All the speed we're bleeding off here.
I wonder if it's enough to actually come down or we have to do another go-around.
Nope.
We're coming down.
But not on the lit side, unfortunately.
Oh, the game almost crashed.
Hopefully, it didn't crash or hopefully it's fine.
Wait, look at this!
It's like a river!
Whoa!
I wish it wasn't night!
I would love to see this.
Oh, man.
What is that over there?
Oh, it's very hard to see.
It's so dark.
Are we gonna land in that river?
No, we're not.
We're chilling.
Chutes are up!
Droges!
Here come the main chute.
Man, textbook.
Okay, you see that there?
Guys, I'm gonna walk over there.
Ah, but it's gonna take forever.
What is that?
One of these days, I'm gonna land next to it.
It'll happen sooner or later.
We just gotta be patient.
Okay, please don't land on a tree.
That would be terrible.
I'm tempted to just jump out with one kerbal and try the personal parachute.
Touchdown!
Good job.
Do I need to take some science here, maybe?
Nah, keep it just in case the mission gets fucked up.
Oh, look at our money!
We have way more than we need!
Okay, not way more, but we have enough.
Luna got experience.
Cargill got nothing.
But I guess that's no...
Or there was nothing new for her there.
Beautiful.
And we even have a new scientist now.
It's not just gonna be Bob anymore.
Oh, by the way, I keep forgetting.
So you can apparently use the middle mouse button to pan the camera.
Next time I fly, I'm gonna try that.
Uh, whoa, whoa, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I need to...
Science.
Oh my god.
We're gonna have a hundred thousand-ish left after this and I think it's fine.
Also, resource transfer available.
I'm excited about that.
Take it.
Oh, it looks different too.
Man, this game is just getting better and better.
Oh, but wait, wait, wait.
Parts also cost money when we buy them here.
We have to be careful not to spend all of our money.
This is actually crucial.
Okay, so what am I gonna get?
We have a whole smorgasbord here.
We have 670 science!
We could just...
take it all!
Heavier rocketry!
Also, can I just...
Okay, I guess we need to get the next stage before we can get this.
Oh no, wait.
Maybe we get this first and then we can get it.
Unless we have to get another stage of research and science or whatever.
Okay, so here...
Mainsail, liquid fuel engine...
Twin boar?
Thoroughbred!
Cheetah.
Oh my god.
Be still, my beating heart.
Be still.
Okay, just more fuel tanks.
Got it.
Specialized construction.
Stampotron!
Ground anchor?
Wait, what is that?
Occasionally, even the most seasoned of rocket jockey wants to be safely back on the ground.
And what better way to securely show your affection for gravity than by clamping yourself to it?
The Stampotron ground anchor provides a secure point to which you can attach other parts with EVA construction including docking ports if you'd like to park a larger vessel safely.
Expect stocks in C7 aerospace division to jump if negative gravity is ever a real thing.
So, EVA construction.
I feel like that's something I should start experimenting with.
And I have a feeling it's related to the, you know, putting, uh, or getting the science behind the goo on the surface of Minmus.
maybe you need to EVA construct a goo canister on the surface or something.
You know?
Clampotron docking...
Is this a bigger one?
Must be.
Because it looks exactly the same.
Like, do I not already have this?
It's gotta be, like, a bigger one.
Radial attachment point.
Originally a defective Clampotron docking port, engineers soon discovered it had great potential as a structural element.
Okay, so it's like a...
Yeah, it's a Clampotron without being able to clamp.
Or it's permanently cramped.
Clamped.
You know what I mean?
Engine plate.
What is this?
Inspired by an upside-down birthday cake.
Now with added shrouds for windy days.
This engine plate provides the best value for funds.
Engine plate.
I feel like I should try that too.
I think I have one of those, actually.
Grip strip?
A large non-slip strip giving unparalleled traction for all your non-slip needs.
Wait, so wait, what if I...
Are you saying I can fly with a Kerbal?
If I put this piece of adhesive or so on my spaceship, I fly the Kerbal into it, I'm gonna stick to it?
I hope that's the thing.
Because that sounds freaking awesome.
And silly.
And I'm all about that.
Advanced Grabbing Unit.
What the hell?
Hinges?
Damn.
Supersonic flight?
At some point, I'm gonna get into this, but I honestly, I'm so...
Like, my excitement for this is, like, negative.
I'm here for rockets, man.
Another heat shield.
Ooh!
Is this, like, a gigantic landing leg?
If so, I may get this.
This is one of them I'm gonna get, I think.
And then this one.
Specialized Control.
Okay, not super excited.
Ooh!
I'm very excited about this.
Lander can...
Oh!
Mooner Excursion Mod...
Dude, we're doing this.
Yoink!
That's the first.
Sequence 9, Container Module.
Capable of storing a wide variety of equipment.
Specifically designed for storing precision scientific instruments and protecting them from the rigors of launch.
Oh, you know what I hope this is?
I hope it's something that is so big that I can put a Science Junior inside of it.
That is my dream.
I'm not sure it is that big, though, but I hope it is.
Oh, that's just another one that's, like, half as big.
Mobile Processing Lab.
Wait, what?
No longer are you limited to research facilities only on Kerben.
With a mobile processing lab, you can conduct long-term experiments and ongoing research with the data you collect in the field.
Be sure to check back on your scientists from time to time and transmit the results of their research home?
This model is guaranteed to spontaneously combust less than previous models and also has the equipment necessary to clean out and restore functionality to inoperable experiments.
Yo, this sounds incredible!
I'm not sure I entirely understand how this works, but I am Omega excited for that.
Scanning arm?
Okay, we're taking this.
That's definitely in the bag.
Precision engineering?
What?
Weather analyzer?
Relay antenna?
Okay, I'm less excited.
Wait, we can get this now?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Wait a sec!
Should we get one of these really expensive ones?
Field science?
External command seat?
Rover wheels?
Scanning tech?
Oh, dude.
Surface scanning module?
Okay, I am so tempted to take this.
The thing I'm afraid of, though, is that if I take this, that some of these are gonna be dependent on something else that I don't have right now, you know what I mean?
God, I hope it's like standalone, it's just gonna work.
But it is expensive.
I can get two of these for the same price.
I could get this one, but do I want this one?
Ah, there's also this, I really want that.
And what is this?
Oh, God, oh, God, uh...
Wait, what is this?
What is that one?
Okay.
Like, precision propulsion.
I guess this would be really good in low-G environments like Minmus.
It's probably, like, extremely efficient, too.
290?
It's not, okay, not that efficient.
Never mind.
Shrimp solid fuel booster.
Like, 310, but...
Okay, never mind.
This one is 250.
Oh, they are way more efficient, then.
Maybe I should go into this.
320 ISP.
That's very good.
And it's kind of cheap.
Okay, you know what?
I'm gonna wait with the 300 section.
I think it's better to get a lot of these things here.
Although, this feels a little less important.
So, for now, there's definitely this one.
I want these landing struts.
There's also a parachute here.
Mark 25?
I'm taking this.
And then, we have 190 left.
I can take...
Okay.
I guess I'm gonna take...
I'm gonna take this.
More battery, you know?
This is also exciting, but it seems...
Or we just get more fuel stuff.
Or, hey, heavier rocketry, maybe?
Hey, we gotta get this.
Boom.
Whoa.
Oh, all these parts cost 147,000?
Ugh.
This is expensive.
Yikes.
Oh my God.
Okay.
You know what?
Let's take a look at the contracts here.
These goddamn stones.
maybe I can do it now since I have surface samples capability.
Right?
Let's see what's available.
Position satellite in an equatorial orbit of Minmus.
Uh.
Alright.
I mean, I guess I can try this.
Build a new unmanned probe that has an antenna and can generate power.
I mean, we gotta get some money, right?
We're kinda short on cash.
Or I try to do Explore Eve.
All we have to do is like a flyby.
I need to tracking station.
Let's figure out where this bastard is.
Oh.
Oh my God.
Wait.
Oh, there it is.
Mono.
Eve.
Duna.
Whoa.
Jewel.
Elu.
Is there more?
No.
Oh my God.
Okay, so...
Wait a minute.
This is gonna be...
Uh.
Hold on.
There was something about that.
Like, I need to...
Transfer windows here.
Space travel.
Maneuvers.
I guess you would have to somehow...
Like, there's no way you just launch a rocket and adjust everything, you know?
Like, you wanna...
You wanna wait for a transfer window.
It's like real life.
Otherwise, it's just impossible.
I mean, you can do it, but...
You almost can't do it, you know?
It doesn't make any sense not to wait.
Um...
Wait, what was I looking for?
I forgot.
Um, I was looking for...
Oh yeah, it's something about transfer windows.
It's not here.
Maybe it's like here?
Definitions...
Map interface...
Maneuver notes?
Wait, I saw this in the UI at some point.
Was it...
I think it was in the vehicle construction facility.
Was it this one?
Create alarm.
That's it.
Planetary transfer window.
Um...
Starting body carbon.
I wanna go to...
Eve.
What?
Wait, are you saying...
I need to wait two years?
Unless...
What's the date right now?
Oh, time off...
Oh, never mind.
Time off is year two, day three.
Oh shit, wait.
This...
Space program is two years old?
What the hell?
So, wait, wait.
Time until...
270 days.
But what does this mean?
37 days.
Wait.
Make no changes to the...
Wait, hold on.
Add alarm.
Okay, so in 270 days.
Okay.
Oh, and I can...
Oh, oh, okay.
Uh...
Damn, that's kind of a long time, isn't it?
Hmm.
I'm gonna assume we need a...
Let me calculate this real quick.
Uh...
A shit ton of fuel!
Let me just bring way more than I think I need.
Uh...
Let's see here.
How would I do this?
Um...
Also, wait, wait, wait.
We also got some new shit to play with.
Let's just...
Play with that.
For a sec.
Let's call this, uh...
Eve...
Um...
Extreme.
Nah, it's not extreme.
This is like, um...
Eve, uh...
The Eve entry.
That's what it is.
We enter.
Uh...
So now we got some new stuff here.
This one I'm excited about.
Let's see this.
2.4 tons.
Damn.
That is...
Oh, it has tolerance of 20 meters per second.
That's...
That's kind of a lot.
I'll take it.
From here it just looks the same size.
But I'm sure it's probably very...
Oh my...
Yeah, that's a big one.
That's a big boy.
But that also...
Can you stop?
Okay, there we go.
Save it.
Uh...
Definitely need a bigger parachute.
Is that what I just got?
We also have this one.
Mark 16 XL.
No, it's gotta be this one.
Ooh, nice.
So let's say we do that.
Oh, wait a sec.
Do I really need three people?
You know what?
Let's keep things simple here.
Let's actually try something.
Let's try...
Let's see how far we can get with like one.
Um...
No, no, no.
I do want to bring a scientist.
If we're going out there, I want to do science, right?
Obviously.
Um...
Wait, I'm actually...
How come the...
How come this one doesn't fit on that?
This is like the second size, you know?
One, two, three.
Just like the pods.
That's kind of weird.
Okay, and then we need two of these.
There we go.
And...
Ah, but wait.
Let's just try and keep mass low.
This is like an experiment more than anything.
Like, we're going...
To a whole other planet.
This is a big one.
I can't take this lightly, you know?
This is...
Okay.
There we go.
We're coming in.
Simple.
Now we need a...
Uh...
Fuel tank.
The...
Wait, there's also this one.
Ah, that's the big one.
Okay.
I can also try to keep it to this size.
All the way.
Let's say I do...
Two of these.
Let's make this white.
Because it looks cool.
That's kind of dope.
Keep it white.
Okay.
Engine.
So we got some new engines.
Look at this.
Cheetah.
So what is...
355 ISP?
It even fits!
Wait.
Uh...
This one has...
330...
310...
300...
Oh, this is a solid booster.
Okay.
Wow!
Wow, so many variations?
The hell?
I kind of like the exposed view.
It looks nice.
Yo, this looks so dope!
You know what?
This actually looks like...
One of the...
First rockets from the Gemini missions.
This big, uh...
Like...
Exhaust, you know?
With this kind of body.
It looks exactly like it.
I'm trying to think what it looked like.
But it looked like this.
That's so cool.
Now we do that.
Wait, what?
Huh?
Aw, what?
Why you gotta be like that?
Ah, okay.
Whatever.
That's fine.
This definitely looks better.
So now...
We're gonna do...
A massive...
Um...
We also have to remember...
We only have 85,000 right now.
We are kinda poor.
I think I do wanna expand into the big...
Boy section here.
And then...
Do these.
We're gonna have...
That.
Let's see what we have here.
So we also got some new engines.
Skiff.
240 at sea level.
Whoa!
1379 at...
Wow.
That's strong.
This one is 1,500.
At sea level.
I kinda want...
Oh, that's 38,000 just for that engine?
Ah, we can't afford that.
Nope.
Skipper.
Wait, hold on.
This one has...
600...
No, 570.
This one is...
Worse.
Why are they so ex...
Okay, maybe I do buy this.
Dude, I need to see this in action.
So wait, 38,000.
That's gonna leave us with...
Almost nothing.
And we have, like, 30,000 left.
Ugh.
I feel like I shouldn't take that risk.
Especially because this may not even fit here.
I don't even know, like...
With that amount of thrust?
I wish I could see, like, a radius on it.
Or, like, a preview.
Like, look.
Six tons.
I'm gonna stick with this.
For now.
And...
What then?
I guess we do boosters.
Is it...
Maybe it's a little too tiny.
Hold on.
Let's just add way more.
Go all the way.
I'm gonna make this orange.
Because it's freaking awesome looking.
Ugh.
So sexy.
There we go.
Look at all the Delta V we already have.
But wait.
There's more.
Thoroughbred fuel booster.
That's 27,000 just to purchase it.
So I can use it.
Just so I can purchase it.
So I can purchase it.
That's too much money.
I think this is...
This is probably fine.
6,000 Delta V.
I have no idea if that's enough for this.
Let's see if we can get even more.
If I do three.
All right.
It's definitely diminishing returns here.
Because we keep adding mass.
Uh...
Oh, wait.
We're all...
Oh, shit.
I forgot about the mass.
Oh, we can't even do this.
What about two?
Can I do two of them?
No!
Oh, God.
Uh...
Wait.
How much does this weigh?
51 tons.
24.
70.
Uh...
That's gonna take us over as well.
But it's also super expensive.
I think we may have to kick back...
And crack open a cold one.
Let me try two of these.
With the kickback.
Kickback action.
Yeah, it's not enough.
But...
Wait, wait.
Now we're at 125.
We can maybe do one more.
Shit!
We're overweight.
But hey.
Maybe we don't need all this liquid fuel.
Maybe we calm down a bit.
Get rid of that.
We just do that.
And then...
That's kind of worse...
Than what I had before.
God damn, dude.
What about four of them?
That looks kind of excessive, doesn't it?
Yeah.
We're also overweight again.
Frick.
But now that I have one less liquid fuel...
Maybe we can have two at least.
That's 100.
Nope.
That's too much.
Man!
Why you gotta be so...
Fat?
Stop!
Okay.
In that case, I'm adding another one of these.
You can't stop me.
And then we take...
Oh, shit.
I didn't mean to destroy that.
Do I actually get all the money back when I do that?
I wonder.
Okay.
And now we do two of these kickbacks.
Why is it so...
Oh, wait.
Okay.
That's better.
Now we move these down.
Actually, I can do...
Brother.
Huh?
The hell?
Okay.
I think this is probably okay.
Sweet.
Make them white.
Okay.
Here's a problem I have, though.
If I do bring two people...
Like, what if I don't have enough to get to Eve?
I guess I can abandon, you know, the plan and come back home.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I guess that's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna add these as well, because they look awesome.
That's the only reason I add them, because they look awesome.
Let me make this...
That color...
Oh, it's so pretty!
Ooh-hoo-hoo!
So nice!
Okay, so now we do...
Uh...
These three together?
Wait, why is it looking like that?
Okay, and then this comes off.
That comes off.
This burns.
Comes off.
Shoots.
Yeah!
I like...
We're not bringing any...
Science.
Simply because...
It's weight, and right now everything is...
Expensive, and you know...
Reasons.
So, I feel like 5,400...
Should we not be able to do better?
We have like...
34...
No, what am I saying?
14 tons left we can add.
Hey, who's saying I can't add smaller ones?
Hold on a minute.
Is that...
Is this dumb?
What about the thumper?
Oh, we're just overweight.
Okay, you know what?
Fuck you!
It's okay.
We're just gonna go.
Is the plan...
It's gonna be...
Let's see.
Let's actually bring Luna.
Luna, you get to...
Oh, look, she already did get some experience.
Man, we only have one pilot.
Oh!
Wait, I know what to do.
I could bring a thingy that has SAS on it.
But needs power.
Do I want to do that?
I even forgot...
Oh, wait, it was this one.
This one, or that one?
It's so tiny.
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah.
This is fine, this is fine.
It's okay.
In fact, we don't even need...
A pilot.
Nah, we need a pilot.
Wait, do we need a scientist for this?
Actually, we don't need a scientist, because we're not gonna do any science.
It's just Cargill.
Cargill, you need to do us proud with this one.
And I think everything is set here.
Yep.
Thrust to weight ratio is 1.4.
That's beautiful.
Eve entry.
You ready?
Here we go.
Let's see...
If we can do this.
If we can do it, there's a lot of money coming in via the contract.
Lift off!
Whoa!
We are heavy.
That's heavy, Doc.
Wait, what's happening to my...
Oh!
Something isn't looking right here.
I gotta be honest.
There's a problem with one of the boosters.
In fact, both boosters are having malfunctionings.
I am actually scared to...
What do you call it?
Disengage them.
Oh my god, this is bad.
What kind of a design is this?
Who designed this shit?
Goddamn engineers.
Back at Kerbal Space Center.
Never can count on them.
I really hope these are gonna separate.
What if we blow up?
Oh!
There goes two of my fins!
Holy shit!
Wow!
That ain't no joke!
We could've blown up there.
Also, we are not even that...
Uh, we may not have enough here.
The thing is, I don't know how much I need.
Also...
I just realized...
I'm an idiot.
We're not even at the transfer window!
But I guess we can orbit until then.
Yeah, never mind.
It's fine.
Oh, you can't...
Oh, wait.
Don't actually time warp now.
That's scary.
Yeah, look at the way we're...
Like, this is...
We're way too low.
I feel like I should've just used the old rocket.
It was better.
It may also have been cheaper.
I don't know.
Absolutely terrible.
44 on APWAPSIS.
Yeah, look at the vector.
It's way...
We gotta go a little...
Higher here.
So, we're pointing this way.
But our actual vector of velocity is this way right now.
And...
There we go.
Now...
Oh, God.
It's so...
I wonder how long it's gonna take to burn with this stage.
Probably not too long, right?
Let's just start burning now.
Oh, my God.
We're not even aligned!
It's not responding at all.
Maybe I need to...
Do we even have...
Wait a second.
We didn't bring, uh...
Extra batteries here.
This could be a problem.
Oh, God.
Will you please align?
Prograde!
It's too heavy.
I need to add a little bit of...
Ugh, come on.
I need gimbling.
Gimble that bastard.
Ugh!
Yeah!
Ugh, you're so heavy.
Jesus Christ.
What did you have for breakfast, Cargill?
Oh, my God.
Hey, we can actually make it to orbit with this stage.
Ooh!
That's actually insane.
This may actually be a better rocket than the other one, then.
Yeah.
Only 200 more.
Oh, we have like 1,000 there.
And...
We should almost be there.
Trying to get the Vectra on the horizon there.
Wait, why is...
Okay, there we go.
There we go.
Alright, this is a terrible orbit.
Terrible orbit.
Shit.
Oh, I really...
Oh, shit.
I should have...
I fucked it up!
Oh, I'm wasting fuel.
Oh, it's horrible.
It's terrible.
What?
We're burning up!
That is...
This is the worst mission of all time!
Oh, my God, bro.
I mean, I can burn all I want right now.
It's not gonna help me.
Oh, shit.
Let's at least reduce drag.
There.
Surface area minimized.
Okay, we're out of...
Okay, good.
We're rising.
Well, that was a kind of disaster, wasn't it?
So, one thing I need to know...
Oh, my God, the inclination is also...
Oh, my God, how are we even gonna do this?
Jesus Christ.
If you think about it, we need to slow down in our orbit around the sun.
Right?
If Periopsis is over there, we're gonna bring that in.
And then somehow have a rendezvous with Eve.
So, obviously, the thing we need to do first is to escape Kerbin's sphere of influence.
We gotta just orbit the sun on our own, so to speak, without being in orbit around Kerbin.
But also...
I'm gonna just click here and see what happens.
I don't know if I need to do, like, a maneuver note.
I'm just gonna see.
Also, we have Carson in orbit around Kerbin in the space center.
Or, sorry, in the space station.
He has plenty of food for a year.
In fact, there's food for many years up there.
It's gonna be fine.
Here we go.
Wait, really?
Wait, I'm confused.
Burn to get us out of the atmosphere.
I'm an idiot.
I forgot to burn on abwapses.
No!
Man, no!
This is getting worse by the minute.
Ah!
All the money in the toilet.
You know what?
Is that...
Wait, what's that?
Wait, dessert?
As in snack?
Dessert?
Launch site?
I don't know if this is intentional or they meant to say desert.
Wait, what is that?
You know what?
Am I gonna...
Shit.
You know what?
Nope.
We're going home.
This mission is...
Bust.
See ya.
This is a total...
I...
Nope.
I'm going home.
We're gonna have to redo this one.
Absolute tragedy that was.
Wow.
Cargill, stop smiling like an idiot.
This is a failure.
It's not a success.
You understand that, right?
You're not going anywhere.
Jesus.
We should be slowing down enough here.
Apoapsis coming down rapidly.
Please take us below...
60-ish on the apoapsis.
And there we go.
We're coming back home.
No go-arounds here.
Wonderful.
Oh my god.
The ablator has a lot up here.
Because it's like a bigger...
Pot.
Or capsule.
What is it actually called?
Pot.
Okay.
Single pea in a pot.
Dude, that's so perfect for this.
They're green.
So when there's two in there, it's two peas in a pot.
Literally.
I can't believe I left all that fuel in...
Well, it's not in orbit, I guess.
It's gonna burn up.
That's gonna be a...
Fireworks situation for sure.
Oh, we're coming right through the clouds.
Whee!
Dang, son.
Whoa!
Oh my god!
Parachutes!
Ooh, it's windy!
Whoa!
I gotta...
Uh...
I'm kinda scared.
There's a storm.
Okay.
We penetrated the cloud.
Main chute.
Wow, it is so foggy here.
Are we over water?
That's gotta be, right?
Is that water?
Yeah, it's water.
Splash down it is.
Man, this looks so good.
Splash down!
In the Pacific Ocean or something.
God, who's gonna go collect us here?
That's gonna be a tough one.
Well, that was a failure.
That's probably the...
The worst mission I've ever done.
Actually, that's not true.
The worst mission has got to be Jebediah working for Clampatron.
Because, you know, he died.
And it was the worst death of all time.
Like, what do you mean?
That's gotta be...
We lost half our money on that!
Okay, wait a minute.
Can I get an advance?
Hello?
I need...
I need money.
What do you want?
I'll do anything.
I'll position a satellite up your ass.
I don't know why I say that.
I'm not usually that mean.
I just lost a lot of money right now, okay?
Okay, you know what?
Position a satellite in an equatorial orbit of Minmus.
I can see myself doing that.
I would love to try and make a satellite.
We actually have two of these.
Look at this.
Oh, that's very specific.
Oh my god.
Within marginal deviation.
Thermometer.
Have a Science Junior on it.
Maintains stability.
This is a lot of money we're gonna get if we do it.
It's not bad.
Okay.
This one is the same, except there's no need for the Science Junior.
Oh my god.
Let's take...
What does that say?
Alright, we can take this one.
That's okay.
We can bring a Science Junior.
Why not?
Is he saying alright?
Sounds like it.
Okay, we got a little advance.
Now we have some money.
Okay, the EVE entry was definitely...
I think the rocket was good.
The rocket was actually excellent.
It's just that, uh...
Let's just say Cargill...
It was not her day.
Alright?
Flying that thing, she had no idea what was happening.
She must have gotten the wrong leg out of the bed in the morning.
Okay, uh...
So now...
We're gonna try and make something completely different.
No.
Don't save.
We can try the ProBodoBodyne StayPutnik.
I guess.
Or this one.
Let me see.
Electric charge 1.2 per minute.
Okay, so we definitely need solar...
Panels.
Which makes sense.
It has a reaction wheel.
Stability assist.
Nice.
And...
What else did we need for that?
Thermometer.
Science Junior.
That's a...
That's kind of large.
But maybe we can do a little funky business.
No.
No funky business.
What about that one?
Hey!
That's too big now.
Okay.
New plan.
I'm gonna take the...
Uh...
Duh-duh-duh-duh-duh...
This one.
Is that smaller or bigger?
Does it fit?
It's so tiny.
Why is it so tiny?
Can we use these?
Give me this.
I like this one more.
I don't like this.
It looks very...
Un-aerodynamic.
This looks better, weirdly.
Because we can put a little thingy on top, right?
Make it sharp.
So now...
Let's see here.
Structural.
Hey!
That works!
That's too big.
Oh my god.
It's not the prettiest thing.
That's okay.
Maybe it doesn't have to be this pretty.
If you think about it, all we need is fuel, right?
Wait a minute!
Let's wait...
Oh, I know what I need!
I know what I need!
I'm gonna call this...
Satellite.
Wait, how do I spell satellite?
I think that's it.
Yeah, two L's.
Save.
I'm gonna get the upgrade.
Oh, do I have enough science?
Ooh!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
But there was precision...
Systems.
Oh, I don't have enough.
Oh, crap.
That's way too big.
I mean, maybe it's not that bad.
You know what?
It's actually not that bad.
Okay, it's kind of bad.
Okay, whatever.
Let's put the science guy in there.
Bill Nye.
Boop!
And now we need some fuel tank.
That seems about right.
Maybe a little more.
Nah, that seems about right.
And this guy...
That looks nice.
Very simple setup here.
Hey, wait a sec.
Nobody...
Oh!
I just had an idea.
Ooh, watch this.
Oh, that's genius.
Uh...
Wait, how do I...
Oh, no.
Yes!
Oh, that's beautiful!
Uh...
Oh, my God.
Angelo.
You're tearing my heart out.
Why can't I move that single piece?
Okay, whatever.
Close it.
Now we put this here.
Oh, my God.
It's gonna be beautiful.
And now at the top, we're gonna add something else.
Jesus.
Heh?
Eh?
Not bad.
Or maybe even...
Hey, that's not bad either.
That's sick!
What a nice little...
Thing I have going here.
And then we add a tiny bit of this.
Ooh, it even...
Alligns.
Okay.
So now we need...
Uh, what was it?
Show me.
Thermometer!
Mmm!
We can put that in here!
Aha!
So that we don't expose it to, you know...
Whatever's gonna happen outside.
Thermometer!
Why are you like this?
Excuse me?
Oh, I can put it on you, of course.
Smart.
I can maybe even snap it.
Bop!
And then...
So these two are check.
So that's all I really needed to bring.
Okay.
Now we need some solar panelus.
Uh, that would be an electrical, I guess.
Oh, maybe also a battery.
Let's bring a battery.
I like that.
We can even, uh...
Honestly, why not just do this?
It's not that bad!
Looks okay!
I like it!
Yeah, I-I-I-I do like it.
Okay, and then?
Photovoltaic panels.
I'm gonna have...
Like that, maybe.
Actually, hold on.
Put these here.
That looks better.
Oh, yeah.
Except they're floating!
That's illegal.
Not on my watch.
Snap.
Although, it does look kind of non-aerodynamic, doesn't it?
Do we have room in here?
Actually, I have an idea.
Take this guy?
Put him like...
Uh, only one of them.
Only one guy.
There.
Nope.
No, no, no, no.
There.
And then we have two of these on this...
Oh, that's perfect.
Look at that.
It's like...
Made for it.
Oops.
Uh, put it like...
There.
Close.
Oh, it perfectly fits too!
Nice!
So now we have plenty of battery.
We got solar panel.
And...
What else?
Oh, let me change this color.
Can I change color in that?
Oh, that's inside, isn't it?
Let's see what it looks like when I change it.
Oh, it like...
It opens it up somehow?
Oh, I actually like that.
It's like on little struts in there.
That looks nice.
You may say...
Nobody's gonna see that.
It's inside there.
But I care.
I will know.
Nah, it's not gonna be orange.
Yes!
We make it black!
And then...
Ooh!
Hey!
That looks amazing!
Wow!
That's beautiful.
Now what?
What about an antenna?
Hello?
If we're making a satellite?
We gotta have an antenna.
Uh...
Maybe we have two of them.
Huh?
That's probably too much.
Let's just have one.
Retract.
Oh, yeah.
In fact, I'm gonna put it on the other side.
Because we're gonna be taking off.
And I would like the weight to be slightly on this side.
So I automatically turn right.
Yeah.
Very nice.
Okay, what else?
Utility.
Wait.
I forgot I got this!
Scanning arm!
What even is that?
The experimental engineering group managed to successfully adapt technologies from several other manufacturers to produce this once-in-a-lifetime piece of technology.
The light scanning arm is capable of independent work on distant planets, analyzing the geology and composition of rocks and other surface features, with two different instruments.
A masterpiece of engineering and design.
13.6 EC per second.
That is expensive.
Wow.
Guys, I gotta get it.
Oh, man.
It looks cool, too.
Haha.
Wait.
Preview scanning range?
What?
Oh, I guess so.
We wanna face?
Okay.
Uh.
Wait a minute.
At that point, we wanna put the satellite into, like, a rotation so that it always faces the surface, right?
This looks really damn cool.
Maybe I'll rotate it.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
What else?
Oh, yeah.
We also have this?
Do we...
Okay.
Let's not overdo it.
This is just a simple mission.
But I'm excited.
Minimus.
Satellite.
Wait.
Is it...
Bro, hold on.
How do I not know how to spell satellite?
Let me Google it.
Satellite.
Oh, it is...
Okay, so I did get it right.
It just looks wrong to me.
I thought I was losing my mind.
In fact, this is gonna be the Minimus scanning satellite.
It's the MSS.
We shall go there and analyze.
Uranus.
No.
Analyze.
But it will analyze very thoroughly inside of there.
Let's add a decouple mechanism.
In fact, we're gonna make this, like, super simple.
Oh, what the...
Huh?
Wait, what?
What'd I just do?
How did I just do that?
Okay, I have no clue.
Oh, wait.
I need to grab this.
Oh.
It's like the parent.
It's like the pod, you know?
This is the pod equivalent.
Okay.
Now.
Now, obviously, we didn't need to bring this, because it's not part of the mission, but I need to see it.
I gotta see it.
Okay.
What else we got?
Yeah, I'm gonna make this simple.
So, here, this is, like, the last stage.
In fact, we're not gonna make it any wider than this.
This is a little...
tiny rocket.
That's it.
And now we put a little guy.
Swivel.
Love to swivel around.
Make this orange.
And...
Yeah.
That looks nice.
Kinda.
Now, how much do we have?
It's not that much delta-v.
So, what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna make it longer.
No.
Let's do...
I'm really starting to love these side thingies.
Like, I really do like the way this feels and looks.
It has a cool factor, doesn't it?
Let's not put it on the separation mechanism.
Let's have it here.
That's more like it.
Gotta move it down.
Yes.
I do wanna move this slightly down as well.
Just so we don't get the...
The bending situation we had last time.
Okay.
This is a simple rocket.
And I think it's enough.
With my skills now, you know, getting to orbit and all that.
We're gonna...
We're gonna slap with this.
Oh!
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, yeah.
We don't need parachutes.
This is all we need, right?
Thermometer.
Check.
Science Junior.
Oh, yeah.
Check.
Yeah.
This is a simple...
Simple satellite.
Launch.
Let's do it.
God, it looks so...
Scientific.
So...
Technic.
That's a...
That's a deep reference right there.
If somebody gets that one...
You're kind of a G.
Kind of wanna slow down a bit here.
Uh-oh.
Oh, shit!
I lost...
I lost control because...
The gimbal!
Oh, no!
Die!
Back up, back up, back up!
Oh, what a path.
What a path.
Ah, shit.
Okay.
I think it's okay.
It's okay.
Oh, it's terrible.
Holy!
What just got this?
Oh, fuck!
Oh, no!
Shit!
Yeah!
Stop!
What is happening with my orbit today?
Come on!
Correct, correct!
Correct!
Come on!
Shit!
Wait, that's it?
Oh, no, wait.
I have another stage.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
This is...
This...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God.
Come on!
We can make it!
I'm not fucking wasting this money.
There's no way.
We gotta go up there.
We're getting up there.
I don't know if we have enough.
We may not have enough.
This is a freaking catastrophe.
It does say 3,000.
That's putting my mind at ease a little.
I can't believe I've done this.
You know what it is?
It's because...
This little, uh...
Thing in there, it doesn't have a lot of reaction wheels.
Uh, you know?
Oh, shit.
Ha!
It even has a little satellite symbol.
Cool.
I'm gonna make a little maneuver here.
We're gonna do this.
Whee!
Until we reach...
Approximately...
Orbit.
There we go.
Wait, what?
Oh!
We should've...
We should've started burning 30 seconds ago.
Yeah, you see the reaction wheel?
It's terrible.
I can't even turn this little piece of crap.
Lesson learned.
We need reaction wheels when we do this.
This is absolutely terrible.
Wow.
The last two missions here have been...
Kind of bad.
I mean, obviously this one is bad, because they don't have a skilled pilot like, uh...
Carjil.
Was it...
Carjil?
Forget her name now.
Carjil.
Yeah.
The gel you put on cars.
Okay.
Come on.
70.
Boom!
Absolutely terrible.
I'll be the first to say it.
Not good.
Now, the mission.
Some kind of special orbit.
Oh, okay.
It's actually good that it's kind of high up.
It's gonna cost less delta V for us.
Argument of periapsis 252 degrees.
Wait, what?
Oh, is that, like...
How far away I am from periapsis?
I'm actually...
I don't remember what argument of periapsis means in this case.
Obviously, it's an angle.
Inclination is zero degrees, so it's completely equatorial.
Let's find out when we get there, shall we?
First things first.
We target...
Minmus.
There we go.
How the fuck did I even get a flyby of that one time when I didn't even have the maneuver thingy?
Like, that was just kind of insane.
Or maybe I think it is now, because I'm getting used to these tools, you know?
Wait, what?
Control locked?
Excuse me?
Wait, I didn't mean to do that.
Fuck.
Oh, close the doors.
Let me see here.
There's something going on with this.
Get rid of that.
Control point?
Control from...
Wait, what?
Wait, hibernation?
I guess you can save some electricity?
On long trips?
But...
I just don't understand...
why I can't do the thing.
Cannot add maneuver.
Control locked?
Is it because we were speeding?
We have plenty of electric charge.
Is it because we don't have a connection?
I guess we don't have any...
Wait, oh, this is a problem.
We don't have any radar systems here.
Maybe there's one coming over the horizon?
Ah, there we go.
Look.
So now I can...
hopefully do it.
Where was it?
There.
So, like here.
Yeah!
Okay.
But wait, wait.
We need to actually fix the...
eccentricity first.
Okay, I saw it.
5.9.
But can you please just...
You bastard!
Okay, now it's pinned.
There we go.
It's showing now.
Nice!
It's showing.
Beautiful.
0.0?
Nice.
Let's just do that first.
So we have 2,000...
Delta V.
That's actually not bad.
Like, I can get behind that.
I'm digging it.
The shovel is out.
I'm ready.
Let's just warp to that.
Oh, the satellite is coming to Minmus!
One minute to burn.
Right there.
Dude, I keep forgetting to hydrate.
Holy shit.
Cheers.
Okay.
40 seconds.
Get ready.
3, 2, 1.
Wouldn't it be nice if we could just deposit all the Delta V at a single instantaneous point in time?
Oh, wait a minute.
Wait, what?
Reset camera.
Oh, it's...
Ah, I see.
When I aim camera...
I thought the vessel was moving for a second, but it's the camera moving.
That is a mindfuck when you do that.
For some reason, I can't do anything with this.
Oh, must be stationary to scan a surface feature.
Oh, wait.
Do you mean, like, stationary orbit?
Or what?
Oh, my God.
Hell, yeah.
Also, we should do this.
It looks like a proper satellite.
Now, we have to start burning towards the moon.
No, not the moon, but a moon.
Minmus.
It's like here.
We're actually almost there.
Oh, that's perfect.
So, wait.
We need it to be...
What was it?
Between 490 and 420.
420.
So, that means we gotta go a little more...
You know what?
Let me do the thing.
So, I click on it first.
Zoom out.
Here.
I mean, that's good, but then...
Oh, my God.
It's so sensitive.
Oh, Jesus.
Move this down.
Okay.
You know what?
It doesn't matter.
We have a periaptive of 90...
Is it 90,000?
I honestly can't tell.
That's good.
I'm happy with that.
We can adjust it from there.
And we have plenty of Delta V.
We're chilling, actually.
What about battery?
We're chilling.
I guess the solar panels are working.
But...
Definitely you wanna bring...
Extra reaction wheels for satellites.
I have learned my lesson.
Because this is...
Absolutely terrible.
Trying to...
Orient this air...
Spacecraft.
Without no gimbal.
Okay.
25 seconds.
And here we go.
I'm coming.
Oh, wait.
Let me try this.
Oh!
Yo.
Hold on.
I need to do this first.
Oh, shit.
Huh?
What happened there?
I gotta turn around.
Oh, look at this.
We can look around.
Okay, there's a limit.
Oh, that's so cool.
Oh, shit.
I turned too much.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, no.
Oh, this is terrible.
I need reaction wheels.
I need real bad.
Okay, start slowing down before we hit it.
There.
And then...
Good enough.
I'm happy with that.
Ooh.
947 Delta V.
Ah, it should be fine.
Minimus is so low mass.
Right?
Like, we should be chilling.
Here we come.
So, satellite is on its way.
And look at this.
Can transmit science.
Signal strength 100%.
Yo, I wonder.
Let's say I were to retract this.
Oh!
Ho-ho!
Ha-ha!
Cool.
So, you absolutely need that.
I guess it makes sense.
Because you have Kerbals on Kerbin.
Who's controlling this probe.
Right?
And they want to be able to have radio contact.
But who knows.
Maybe it was pre-programmed.
The whole path was pre-programmed.
Except I'm making adjustments as we go along.
But we can pretend.
You know?
Oh, yeah.
There we go.
Oh, it even shows me.
Look at that!
Oh, that's cool.
I was wondering, like...
Well, that's nice.
Let's wait until we get over here.
Also, we're definitely not even...
Yeah, the inclination is already fucked.
That's what happens when gravity tucks you in weird directions.
And you aren't exactly precise.
Okay, so we're here now.
Let's burn retrograde.
Gotta slow the hell down.
Why is it wobbling?
Okay.
Oh, it even shows me ascending.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Can I target it somehow?
I guess I can't.
The question is...
I wonder what is more efficient.
Changing, ascending, or, like, inclination further out?
I'm actually not sure.
I have no intuition for this right now.
Huh.
That's interesting.
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna burn retro here.
Until...
I get to the same...
elevation.
Ish.
Like that.
And then when I get over there...
Then I do it.
But wait.
I just...
I...
I misclicked!
Blah-blah-blah!
Fuck!
No!
Oh, I'm coming for you.
We only have 600?
Delta V left.
Come on.
Wait, am I burning the wrong way again?
You gotta be shitting me.
What?
Like, I am...
This is going horrible.
Come on, man.
Pull yourself together.
Dude, I'm...
I'm going the wrong way!
Wait, no, I'm not.
No, I'm not.
We're fine.
Okay.
Ah, shit.
Ah.
Wish me luck!
So, we want to find...
Exactly where they...
There's gotta be a way to...
Target that.
What's that?
Oh!
It's Luna's crap.
Ha ha ha!
Ah, shit, man.
Oh, wait.
What am I doing?
Let's just maneuver note this shit.
Why am I trying to...
Hand fly this bastard?
Hello?
So, we go over here.
Let's find out where they cross.
It's like...
Oh, I guess it'll show me.
Well, it won't really show me.
I'm gonna say, like, there.
Wait, what?
Unset target?
Oh.
Yeah, okay.
Bro, this is horrible.
I'm gonna have to burn on periapsis here.
I just need to bring this down a bit.
I can't focus.
Here we go.
Come on, baby.
Okay.
Not bad.
Now, descending note.
Is that the next one?
It is.
Right there.
Maneuver.
We're gonna have to go up here.
Boop.
That's good.
Only 5.5?
That's so cheap.
Oh.
I'm gonna pre-position myself.
Right there.
Here we go.
We still have a lot of Delta V left, actually.
I think we got this in the bag.
Okay, one minute.
And...
Burn.
That was way too much, wasn't it?
I forgot I had...
Shit.
I'm gonna burn opposite real quick.
Real quick.
Come on.
Why did I press set?
Why did I do it?
Why?
Come on.
Now.
Now we gotta just bring in...
Or bring out.
Take out.
Pizza.
I'm burning...
Prograde.
Plenty of electric charge.
Come on.
Turn around.
That's it.
We don't need a lot.
That's too much.
Shit.
How is that too much already?
The gravity really is low here.
Come on.
Just a little bit.
Oh.
Ah.
Perfect.
Now, is it good enough?
Maintain stability for 10 seconds.
I mean...
Okay.
It was quite a big range.
It should be okay.
We are stable, aren't we?
Yeah!
Wait, wait, wait.
This is not happy.
This one is unhappy with it.
Why are you unhappy?
Oh, I'm at 492 APO apps.
That's crazy.
Wait, really?
Yeah, okay, okay.
So, I guess we just burn a little bit like this.
There we go!
That should be it!
10 seconds.
Come on.
Ah, but wait a minute.
It's the argument of periapsis, I think.
252.
How the fuck would I know?
Hold on.
Between 426...
Inclination 0 degrees.
I mean, 0.2 is it...
Maybe it needs to be really perfect.
Maybe I just need to match this freaking thing right here.
Like...
Oh, I see!
I think they want my APO appsis to be exactly there?
Wait.
Let me move to here.
I'm actually so confused.
Oh!
Oh, argument of periapsis is there!
Bro, I don't know what that means.
Remind me what that is.
Wait.
Let me actually try and burn here and see.
Let me get this a little higher.
Did it change?
I didn't pay attention.
It did change.
But now I'm a little too late.
Oh!
Move it around.
I'm gonna go to this APO appsis here.
And then bring it in a bit.
But I have to be ready to...
Like, it's so sensitive.
Okay!
I see.
So it really just wanted me to be exactly on that.
I thought it was a little...
Like, I thought I had some wiggle room, you know?
Because it said between 420 and 490.
So that's...
That's what confused me.
Okay, well...
We can transmit stuff from here.
Oh, that's actually sick.
Let me try that.
So now we are in a stable orbit.
And I guess this one is not gonna work.
Wait, same...
What does this same vessel interaction mean?
Yeah, it says...
Must be stationary to scan a surface feature.
You know what it also could mean?
Maybe this is not supposed to be on...
On a spacecraft.
Maybe this is supposed to be on a rover, actually.
Now that I think about it.
Maybe that's what they mean by stationary.
I think this is a rover thing.
You know what I...
So when they showed the little bubble...
It makes sense in my mind now that it's like...
That's the actual...
Actual range of the arm.
But I thought it was like...
Oh, it's the field of view.
It's like you have to angle it that way.
That's like...
The field of view that you can see.
That's not what it is.
Oh my god.
That's so stupid.
I can't believe it.
Oh well.
Hey, you live and learn, right?
Okay, so now...
Where is Kerbin?
Over there.
So, yeah.
Look at this antenna.
It's pointed right at it.
What can I do here now?
KerbNet!
Field of view.
Let's bring that in.
Wait, there's a question mark!
Huh?
What do you mean?
Question mark?
Can I zoom more?
I guess I gotta get closer.
But we're kind of in a...
Big orbit right now.
Did I place it?
Oh...
Wait.
Let me orbit a bit more.
Hello!
You can see the stars in the background too!
That's funny.
Was that...
Wait, was that the same question mark?
It just disappeared.
Weird.
The thing is, we're not gonna get the entire surface area like this.
We would need to...
Polar...
Polar orbit for this as well.
If we were to actually...
Oh!
What's happening?
To ensure that you have a reliable communications link with Kerbal Space Center.
Oh!
Do I not?
No probe control.
Oh, wait!
The sun is there!
Solar panels are not even angled at it!
I'm an idiot!
Uh-oh!
That's crazy, bro.
But why is it flickering like that?
It's like it's...
Maybe trying to charge?
There's a little surface area.
There's actually none.
If I only had rotated this slightly this way.
That's crazy.
Wait, let me just go further.
Maybe that's like an angle somewhere.
But no, I mean...
Space is so vast.
There's no way.
We're gonna be at the exact same angle at all times.
Oh my god, that's crazy.
No, but I was looking for question marks.
You can't do this to me.
No!
I really used all my battery?
Wait, flow priority?
Oh, I guess I can...
Prioritize certain batteries...
To be...
Used first.
Wait, I wonder.
Does this have an alternator?
No.
Damn.
Wow.
I wonder if I can come up here and...
Charge it up, you know?
Well, I guess what I could do is bring a...
Kerbal...
And fly into these flaps here.
And have it rotate that way so you can get some...
Surface area on the...
Solar panels.
Oh man, what?
Hey, at least we got the mission done.
So if I go back, I should be able to just...
Collect on that, right?
Let's see.
I should be able to.
200,000?
I think we may have done it.
Let's warp to sunrise.
Wonderful.
Uh...
Duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh.
Yeah.
Nice.
Test mammoth liquid fuel engine on an escape trajectory out of Minmus.
Mammoth?
That sounds like a big boy.
Wait, Jaime.
Lannister.
Crisfree.
What are these names?
Plant a flat...
Come on, man.
I've done that.
Attach a new part to satellite in orbit of Kerbin.
Oh!
Send a Kerbal engineer on a craft and attach a C-200 rechargeable battery bank to the target.
I would love to do that!
Oh!
So I guess that's what engineers do.
That's what they're for.
Yo, we're gonna do this.
Attach C-200 rechargeable battery bank on the aging Kerbin STX satellite 1DL.
Wait, what?
I thought I would have to put it on my own thingy.
But this sounds awesome.
And it's a lot of money, too.
I'll take that.
Can I see that?
Wait, what?
Oh, that's it.
Wait, can I fly that?
Wait, what?
It looks like a freaking satellite!
Oh, this is so cool, man.
I'm taking notes here.
Wow!
Wow, that's cool.
Oh my god, it's so creative.
I need to up my game here.
Oh my goodness.
Look at all this.
Huge!
Oh, they also covered it all the way around.
See, that's smart.
That's something I should have thought about.
Damn it.
This is a smart design.
My design?
Not so much.
Okay, so this is kind of a crazy orbit here.
Let me see what kind of orbit it is.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
Watch this down here.
Oh!
Haha, of course.
That's Carson.
He's there.
Wait, Carson is a pilot.
Maybe it's time we bring Carson home.
You know?
We kind of need him in the space program.
Maybe we rotate somebody else up there.
I think I like that.
In fact, so we bring an engineer up here to this satellite.
We attach the thing we need to attach.
And then we get out of there again.
And we join up with this down here.
And then we exchange places with Carson.
It's like how they do it on the ISS, you know?
They send up a little capsule and it docks with the ISS and a new crew is rotating in.
That's what we're gonna do.
Very nice.
Ah.
Guys.
That's gotta be it for now, though.
We have plans for next time.
We have big plans.
And we also gotta go to Eve.
What do you think of that?
This was so much fun.
This may be my favorite session of the game so far.
Something about it.
It's just...
It's feeling so grand.
Especially when I was trying to get to Eve and I fucked it all up and stuff.
That just gave me even more motivation, you know?
It's like, damn, there's so much out there and we gotta think about that too.
And, oh.
Damn.
Your flips were cool, right?
Yeah.
Bob has it.
Honestly, kind of impressive for a scientist, but, you know.
Turn it down a bit.
Okay.
I'm just gonna quickly save the game so I don't forget.
Also, I think maybe I should make a backup of my save or something.
You know that one time in Minecraft when I...
If I didn't have the backup, I would have lost something.
I'm kind of scared of this being corrupted or whatever.
Especially because I'm modding it so much, you know?
Makes me nervous.
Oh my god.
Kerbal Space Program, ladies and gentlemen.
It is an incredible game.
You need to play it if you haven't.
It is so rewarding when you do things in this game.
It feels so good.
Tunic vibes.
Yeah.
Let me actually put another tunic on here.
I like this one a lot too.
I think it's the menu.
Yeah.
How big is the install?
Good question.
Let me see.
With all the mods I've added, I don't know.
Ah, I'll check later.
Some other time.
I would assume it's not that much bigger than a base game install.
I mean, adding mods really doesn't really add any significant space, right?
It's mostly just code.
I hope you add this track to the in-game playlist.
You think that would fit?
I guess...
Yeah, I could see that.
It could fit a little bit.
It's very spacey...
Spacious, right?
And spacey feeling.
Hey, I'm glad to hear that just Martani.
Well, I'm not glad to hear that you're sick, but I'm glad to hear that I could help with that.
feel better.
I thought I was getting a little sick today because I kept having this like lump in my throat.
You know, like felt like mucus or something.
I don't know what it was, but it was hella annoying.
And that's usually the sign that I'm getting sick or something.
Hopefully it's not going to happen.
Please upload it on YouTube.
Yeah, I'm going to upload it immediately, Afi.
It should be up pretty fast because Kerbal Space Program doesn't take up much in terms of bitrate for some reason.
I guess it's mostly black, you know, when you're in space.
Not much to encode.
Yeah, lots of black void.
Jaggi's doing great.
Honestly, she's never eating her food, man.
Like every time I need to feed her, she always has like maybe 15% left.
I'm going to feed her right after this.
She's actually sleeping.
She's right next to me.
She's in her little bed.
How's my laundry doing?
Yo, actually, my laundry's doing a little weird because I took it out of the washing machine and it was extremely wet.
Now, you might say obviously it's wet.
It just got washed.
But it's like way more wet than it usually is when it comes out of there.
So I don't know if something went wrong.
So I hung it up.
It's fine.
I mean, it's not dripping, but it's like almost.
That was kind of weird.
My cat also does not eat a lot.
Interesting.
I thought cats loved food, you know?
Just like dogs, like they go crazy for it.
But apparently not everyone.
Yeah, I can't put movie music.
I would have, trust me, I would have put interstellar music in this rotation if I could.
That would, I mean, that would be perfect, right?
The docking!
We gotta put the docking music on.
And then I definitely would have said, come on, Tars!
But you can download a music mod where you can add your own music.
And then you can do it if you're playing it on your own.
Kazoo?
Oh, is that the one where they go, uh, I don't even remember what it sounds like now.
But it's like these really shitty instruments.
Carson needs a fade.
Doesn't he already have a fade?
Like, aren't they all like buzz cuts?
All the kerbals have the same haircut.
It's like army cut.
Make all your kerbals bald.
Why?
Oh, so they become more aerodynamic, maybe?
That's an argument.
There's a mod that adds more models to kerbals.
Oh!
Okay, maybe I'll check that out.
You know what the name is?
I would definitely just have a look at least.
It's not kerbals, is it?
Is it actually called kerbals?
I noted it down.
I kind of, I feel like you're fucking with me, but, I mean, I'll find it.
Shouldn't be that hard to find.
You should consider adding the new Ace Combat game.
But I've never played any Ace Combat games, Shev N7.
I would love to.
It's like, like fighter planes, no?
And I love flying in games.
So maybe it would be something for me.
Oh, guys, did you see the new Star Wars game that came out?
The one, pretty much, spiritual successor to Star Wars Episode I, Racer?
I had, like, a blast from the past when I saw that announcement because I totally forgot I played that game as a child.
That was such a good game.
Yeah, it looks incredible.
I saw a little bit of gameplay from it and it's like, wow.
That takes me right back.
I don't know what it's called now.
The new game, but it's like, I guess something about Razer, Star Wars Razer.
So, so good.
Everyone's streaming it today.
Yeah, it just came out, right?
Diverse Kerbal heads.
Okay, I figured it wasn't Kerbalts.
I would have thought you were a Star Trek person.
I'm not one or the other.
I mean...
Okay, listen, I like Star Wars.
I think they're great movies.
I'm not, like, a hardcore fan or something.
I like them.
And I like the Star Trek movies from 2009.
Especially the first.
I don't know, not so much the others, but the first one there was really good.
That was my introduction to Star Trek.
So I was like, oh, this is great, you know?
Then I tried watching the first Star Trek series, like, the first ever.
Man, that has not aged well.
I stopped after, like, three episodes.
Like, it's too old, man.
This is...
I don't know.
Maybe if I watched more, I could have done it, but, you know.
So I feel like the universe is intriguing me.
I love the whole Spock thing, you know, where he's all logical and stuff.
That sounds awesome.
I just feel like I was born at the wrong time maybe to enjoy that.
If I had seen those earlier, maybe I would have enjoyed them more.
TNG is the new generation.
TNG season three is the best play...
What?
So what, you're saying I should check out a specific series from Star Trek and start with the third season?
I'm gonna press X to doubt on that one.
Like, wouldn't I be missing story if I do that?
That sounds like a terrible idea.
I mean, if I start with the TNG, I would start with season one, no?
Somewhat aged, but not that badly.
Okay.
Okay, so what would you suggest, Afi?
If you were to tell me, what should I start with Star Trek?
Because I actually, I am looking for like a new show to watch.
Would be nice to have some sci-fi.
The Orville?
Haven't heard that.
Wait, that's Star Trek?
Wait, how many shows are there in Star Trek universe?
What the hell?
Oh, it's from 2017 as well.
I've never heard of this.
Never.
Uh, hold on.
Hope you're having a good day.
Thank you, Electric Gelato.
You as well.
I just joined now.
How long until you think this is on YouTube?
Uh, since this is a very low bitrate recording, I would say depending on how fast YouTube processes and checks for copyright stuff and all that, maybe like one hour?
One and a half hours maybe?
At the max?
Unless it really shits itself.
Sometimes that happens.
Sometimes I upload the thing and it says checks are running and it says 12 hours left.
And then I upload the same thing and it says checks are running 12 minutes left.
Like, what?
So sometimes I have to give it a little nudge.
It's weird.
The Orville is Star Trek parody that did Star Trek best.
What the?
I'm...
Okay.
Sounds complicated to get into Star Trek.
I don't stream on YouTube.
Okay.
I'm gonna go feed my cat.
I'm gonna feed myself.
I'm gonna feed the man outside my window because he's just not leaving until I feed him, I guess.
Thank you for watching.
I'll see you in the next one.
Something special coming up soon, by the way.
Something none of you are gonna expect, I think.
But yeah.
Have a wonderful day.
Bye-bye.